<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Root>
  <Event>
    <Id>1</Id>
    <Name>GoodTarabala</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>Good Tarabala, good strength of constellation</Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>2</Id>
    <Name>BadTarabala</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>Bad Tarabala, bad strength of constellation</Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>3</Id>
    <Name>GoodChandrabala</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      To be at its best, the Moon should not
      occupy in the election chart, a position that happens to
      represent the 6th, 8th or 12th from the persons Janma Rasi
    </Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>4</Id>
    <Name>BadChandrabala</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      To be at its best, the Moon should not
      occupy in the election chart, a position that happens to
      represent the 6th, 8th or 12th from the persons Janma Rasi
    </Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>5</Id>
    <Name>SiddhaYogaSunday</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Sunday coinciding with the 1st, 4th, 6th, 7th or 12th lunar day and ruled
      by the constellations Pushya, Hasta, Uttara, Uttarashadha, Moola,
      Sravana or Uttarabhadra gives rise to Siddha Yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>6</Id>
    <Name>SiddhaYogaMonday</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Monday identical with the 2nd, 7th or 12th lunar day and with the
      constellations Rohini, Mrigasira, Punarvasu, Chitta, Sravana,
      Satabhisha, Dhanishta or Poorvabhadra produces Siddha Yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>7</Id>
    <Name>SiddhaYogaTuesday</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Tuesday falling on a day ruled by Aswini, Mrigasira, Chitta, Anuradha,
      Moola, Uttara, Dhanishta or Poorvabhadra gives rise to Siddha Yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>8</Id>
    <Name>
      SiddhaYogaWednesday
    </Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Wednesday coinciding with Bhadra and Java and with the constellations
      Rohini, Mrigasira, Aridra, Uttara, Uttarashadha or Anuradha generates
      Siddha Yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>9</Id>
    <Name>SiddhaYogaThursday</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Thursday identical with the 4th, 5th, 7th, 9th, 13th or 14th lunar day and
      with tne asterisms Makha, Pushya, PunarvasJ, Swati. Poorvashadha,
      Poorvabhadra, Revati or Aswini gives rise to Siddha Yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>10</Id>
    <Name>SiddhaYogaFriday</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Friday ruled by Aswini, Bharani, Aridra, Uttara, Chitta, Swati,
      Poorvashadha or Revati coinciding with Nanda and Bhadra constitutes
      this beneficial yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>11</Id>
    <Name>SiddhaYogaSaturday</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Saturday falling on a day ruled by Swati, Rohini, Visakha, Anuradha,
      Dhanishta or Satabhisha and with lunar days Bhadra and Riktha
      generates the same auspicious yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>12</Id>
    <Name>AmritaSiddhaYoga</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Sunday to Saturday respectively coinciding with the constellations
      Hasta, Sravana, Aswini, Anuradha, Pushya, Revati and Rohini will give
      rise to Amita Siddha Yoga.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>13</Id>
    <Name>PanchangaSuddhi</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Panchanga Suddhi. - We have already said that a Panchanga
      consists of tithi, vara, nakshatra. yoga and karana. All these must be
      auspicious. In regard to lunar days, the 4th, 6th, 8th, 12th and 14th, full
      and new moon days should be avoided. In regard to vara, Thursday and
      Friday are held to be suitable for all works. Tuesday, is to be generally
      avoided except when it happens to be the 10th, 12th or 16th day of the
      child's birth when the child's Namakarana (baptising or giving name)
      may be performed. Of the several Nakshatras, Bharani and Krittika
      should be avoided for all auspicious works as these two are said to be
      presided o ver by the god of death (Yama) and the god of fire (Agni) respectively. In urgent cases if the Lagna could be fortified, the dosha
      due to nakshatra may get neutralised. The last parts of Aslesha,
      Jyeshta and Revati should also be avoided. Coming to the Yoga (vide
      page 12) the 6th (Atiganda). 9th (Soola). 10th (Ganda), 17th (Vyatipata)
      and 27th (Vydhruti) have deleterious effects upon events which are
      started or commenced under them. - The Karana chosen must be
      appropriate to the election in view. Thus Bava is auspicious for starting
      works of permanent importance while Thaithula is propitious for
      marriage. Bhadra is unfit for any good work but is eminently suitable for
      violent and cruel deeds. For getting initiation into kshudra mantras
      Sakuni Havana is propitious.
      Therefore, Panchanga Suddhi means a good lunar day, a beneficial
      weekday, an auspicious constellation, a good yoga and a fertilising
      Karana.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>14</Id>
    <Name>UgraYoga</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Any treatment commenced under Ugra yogas are supposed to prove
      successful. Ugra yogas arise when the 3rd (or 9th), 4th, 5th, 6th, 7th,
      9th, 10th, 12th (or 3rd) and 13th lunar days coincide respectively with
      Rohini, Uttara, Sravana, Mrigasira. Revats, Krittika, Pushva, Anuradha.
      Krittika (or Makha).
    </Description>
    <Tag>Medical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>15</Id>
    <Name>SuryaSankramana</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      The 2nd great evil is Surya Sankramana or the
      solar ingress into different zodiacal signs. When the Sun is about to
      leave one sign and enter another there seem to occur certain
      disturbances in the organisation of the solar forces and such times are
      not recommended for any good work. On the contrary, they are held to
      be propitious for meditation, initiation into secret mantras and
      performance of certain religious rites which are held to purify not only
      the bodily electrical discharges but also the mental currents. Sixteen
      ghatis (6 hours 24 minutes) both before and after the entry of the Sun
      into a new sign should be rejected for all new works.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>16</Id>
    <Name>CustomEvent</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>Good tarabala &amp; good chandrabala</Description>
    <Tag>Debug</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>17</Id>
    <Name>KarthariDosha</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Karthari means scissors. In an election, when two
      evil planets are placed on either side of the Lagna, the combination
      goes under the special name of Karthari Dosha and it should be
      rejected for good work particularly in regard to marriage.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>18</Id>
    <Name>ShashtashtaRiphagathaChandraDosha</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Shashtashta Riphagatha Chandra Dosha. - The Moon should
      invariably be avoided in the 6th, 8th and 12th houses from the Lagna
      rising in an election chart.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>19</Id>
    <Name>SagrahaChandraDosha</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Sagraha Chandra Dosha. - The Moon's association (conjunction) with any other
      planet, benefic or malefic, should be avoided. This injunction is specially
      applicable in case of marriage.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>20</Id>
    <Name>UdayasthaSuddhi</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Udayasta Suddhi. - The Lagna and the seventh should be strong.
      The Lagna should be occupied by its own lord and the Navamsa Lagna by its own lord or vice versa or lord of Lagna should aspect Navamsa
      Lagna and vice versa. Similarly the seventh and the lord of the seventh
      Bhava should be favourably disposed. The strength of Lagna and the
      seventh is necessary in all elections but especially so in regard to
      marriage.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>21</Id>
    <Name>SiddhaYoga</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      When a certain weekday coincides with a certain asterism and a certain
      lunar day, it becomes specialy auspicious for good work.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>22</Id>
    <Name>SakunaKarana</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>For getting initiations into mantras Sakini Karana is propitious</Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>23</Id>
    <Name>BadNithyaYoga</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Coming to the Yoga the 6th (Atiganda). 9th (Soola). 10th (Ganda), 17th (Vyatipata)
      and 27th (Vydhruti) have deleterious effects upon events which are
      started or commenced under them.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>24</Id>
    <Name>LagnaThyajya</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Even when the ascendant is strong, certain parts of it which go
      under the name of Lagna tyajya should be rejected. In Aries, Taurus, Sagittarius and Virgo, the first three degrees should be
      avoided as it is supposed to be in the nature of a serpent (bhujanga)
      and hence destructive. In regard to Pisces, Capricorn, Cancer and
      Scorpio, the last (three degrees) has to be avoided as it is supposed to
      be presided over by the evil force of Rahu. The middle half ghati (13°
      30' to 16° 30') should be rejected with regard to Gemini, Libra, Leo and
      Aquarius as it is ruled by an evil force termed Gridhra.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>25</Id>
    <Name>GoodPanchaka</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      For matters of ordinary importance
      such as interviewing superiors or going on short journeys, a favourable
      Tarabala will do and there is no need to consider the panchaka. But in
      regard to very important ceremonies such as marriage, nuptials, entry
      into new houses, etc., this should be carefully looked into.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>26</Id>
    <Name>BadPanchaka</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      For matters of ordinary importance such as interviewing superiors or going on short journeys,
      a favourable Tarabala will do and there is no need to consider the panchaka. But in
      regard to very important ceremonies such as marriage, nuptials, entry
      into new houses, etc., this should be carefully looked into.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>27</Id>
    <Name>BadTaraChandraPanchaka</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>Very bad time for any important works. Bad tarabala, bad chandrabala and bad panchaka.</Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>28</Id>
    <Name>GoodTaraChandraPanchaka</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>Very good time for any important works. Good tarabala, good chandrabala and good panchaka.</Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>29</Id>
    <Name>BadTaraChandra</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>Generally bad time for important works. Bad tarabala &amp; bad chandrabala </Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>30</Id>
    <Name>GoodTaraChandra</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>Generally good time for important works. Good tarabala &amp; good chandrabala </Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>31</Id>
    <Name>BhriguShatka</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      The position of Venus in the 6th is injurious. This is
      especially so in regard to marriage. Even when Venus is exalted and
      associated with benefics, such a disposition is not approved.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>32</Id>
    <Name>Kujasthama</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Mars should be avoided in the 8th house, as it
      indicates destruction of the object in view. In a marriage election chart.
      Mars in the 8th is unthinkable. Even if Mars is otherwise powerful, he
      should not occupy the 8th house.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>33</Id>
    <Name>GoodHairCutting</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Shaving may be had in the constellations
      of Pushya, Punarvasu, Rcvati, Hasta, Sravana,
      Dhanista, Mrignsira, Aswini, Chitta, Jyeshta,
      Satabliislia and Swati. 4th, Gth and 14th lunar
      days as also New Moon and Full Moon days
      arc not desirable. And solar and lunar eclipses.
    </Description>
    <Tag>HairNailCutting</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>34</Id>
    <Name>GoodNailCutting</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Avoid Fridays and Saturdays - the 8th, 9th, 14th lunar
      days as well as New and Full Moon days.
    </Description>
    <Tag>HairNailCutting</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>35</Id>
    <Name>FixedConstellationRuling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Rohini, Uttara, Uttarashadha and Uttarabhadra are supposed to be fixed
      constellations and they are favourable for coronations, laying the
      foundations of cities, sowing operations, planting trees and other
      permanent things.
    </Description>
    <Tag>RulingConstellation</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>36</Id>
    <Name>SoftConstellationRuling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Chitta, Anuradha, Mrigasira and Revati are soft constellations. They are
      good for wearing new apparel, learning dancing, music and fine arts,
      sexual union and performance of auspicious ceremonies.
    </Description>
    <Tag>RulingConstellation</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>37</Id>
    <Name>LightConstellationRuling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Aswini, Pushya, Hasta and Abhijit are light constellations, and they can
      be selected for putting ornamentation, pleasures and sports,
      administering medicine, starting industries and undertaking travels.
    </Description>
    <Tag>RulingConstellation</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>38</Id>
    <Name>SharpConstellationRuling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Moola, Jyestha, Aridra and Aslesha are sharp in nature and they are
      favourable for incantations, invoking spirits, for imprisonment, murders,
      and separation of friends.
    </Description>
    <Tag>RulingConstellation</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>39</Id>
    <Name>MovableConstellationRuling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Saravana, Dhanishta, Satabhisha, Punarvasu and Swati are movable
      stars and they are auspicious for acquiring vehicles, for gardening and
      for going on procession.
    </Description>
    <Tag>RulingConstellation</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>40</Id>
    <Name>DreadfulConstellationRuling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Pubba, Poorvashadha and Poorvabhadra, Bharani and Makha are
      dreadful stars and they are suitable for nefarious schemes, poisoning,
      deceit, imprisonment, setting fire and other evil deeds.
    </Description>
    <Tag>RulingConstellation</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>41</Id>
    <Name>MixedConstellationRuling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Krittika and Visakha are mixed constellations and during their
      influences, works of day-to-day importance can be undertaken.
    </Description>
    <Tag>RulingConstellation</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>42</Id>
    <Name>BadForStartingAllAgriculture</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      While beginning all agricultural operations, see that the 8th house is unoccupied.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>43</Id>
    <Name>LagnaLordIsWeekdayLord</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      Lagna owned by the planet who is lord of the weekday in question.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>44</Id>
    <Name>GoodLunarDayAgriculture</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      All odd lunar days except the 9th are good. All even tithis except the 2nd and 4th should be avoided.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>45</Id>
    <Name>BadLagnaForAllAgriculture</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Gemini: Not favourable for any planting being a barren sign.
      Leo: Not good for any planting, especially bad for underground plants such as potato.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>46</Id>
    <Name>GoodYogaForAllAgriculture</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good yoga for all agriculture is formed when:
      1. A good lunar day for planting
      2. Lagna owned by the planet who is lord of the weekday
      3. Beginning all agricultural operations, see that the 8th house is unoccupied
      4. No malefic rising sign (Gemini and Leo)
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>47</Id>
    <Name>GoodAnySeedsSowing</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Any seeds can be sown on a day ruled by Hasta,
      Chitta, Swati, Makha, Pushyami, Uttara, Uttarashadha, Uttarabhadra,
      Rohini, Revati, Aswini, Moola or Anuradha provided the lunar day is
      also propitious. Choose a Lagna, owned by the planet who is lord of the
      weekday in question.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>48</Id>
    <Name>Ekadashi</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      It is the 11th tithi. Special religious significance in Hindu tradition, usually it's observed by fasting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>49</Id>
    <Name>NotAuspiciousDay</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Tuesday and Saturday should be avoided for all good and auspicious works.
      Tuesday is not evil after midday
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>50</Id>
    <Name>GoodPlanetsInLagna</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Venus, Mercury or Jupiter in the ascendant will completely destroy all other adverse influences.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>51</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingFloweringPlants</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting flowering plants when Virgo is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>52</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingGarlic</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting garlic when Aries is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>53</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingPeachAndOthers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting peach, plum, potatoes, radishes, onion sets and turnips when Taurus is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>54</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingTomatoesAndOthers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting beans, cabbage, corn, cucumber, lettuce, melons, pumpkins, tomatoes, cauliflower,
      water melons, and cereals when Cancer is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>55</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingGrains</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting wheat, rye, barley, rice and other field crops when Libra is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>56</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingOnionAndOthers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting garlic and onion seeds when Scorpio is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>57</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingPepperAndOthers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting Pepper and other spring crops and garlic when Sagittarius is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>58</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingPotatoAndOthers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting potato, radishes and turnips when Capricorn is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>59</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingGrainsAndOthers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting all black cereals and grains when Aquarius is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>60</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingPumpkinsAndOthers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting cucumbers, pumpkins, radishes, water-melons and carrots when Pisces is rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>61</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingTrees</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting trees in Rohini
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>62</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingSugarcane</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Good for planting sugarcane in Punarvasu
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>63</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingFlowerSeeds</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Seeds of flower plants, and fruit-bearing creepers should be sown in the asterisms of
      Mriyusira, Punarvasu, Hasta, Chitta, Swati, Anuradha and Revati
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>64</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingFruitTrees</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Seedlings of long-lived fruit trees when Jupiter is in Lagna on Thursday
      OR
      Fruit trees may be planted when Sagittarius and Pisces are rising on Thursday
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>65</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingFlowerTrees</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Seedlings of flower trees when Venus is in Lagna on Friday
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>66</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingFlowers</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Seedlings of flower sown when Mars is in Lagna on Tuesday
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>67</Id>
    <Name>GoodForPlantingFlowerCuttings</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Flower seeds and cuttings may be sown when Taurus or Libra rising
      and general good time for planting.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>68</Id>
    <Name>GoodRullingConstellation</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Pushya rulling is a constellation par excellence that could
      be universally employed for all purposes, excepting of course marriage
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>69</Id>
    <Name>BadRullingConstellation</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Certain constellations, apart from their being harmonious or otherwise disposed
      with reference to one's own Janma Nakshatra, should be avoided for
      certain specific purposes on account of their inherent evil natures. In
      fact, Bharani is condemned for all good work and it has to be
      scrupulously avoided for all good work.

      When a constellation like
      Bharani(beta Arietis) is held to be constitutionally unfit for certain types
      of elections; it means that the vibrations emanating from it are
      destructive in character

      Of the several Nakshatras, Bharani and Krittika
      should be avoided for all auspicious works as these two are said to be
      presided over by the god of death (Yama) and the god of fire (Agni)
      respectively. In urgent cases if the Lagna could be fortified, the dosha
      due to nakshatra may get neutralised. The last parts of Aslesha,
      Jyeshta and Revati should also be avoided.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>70</Id>
    <Name>GoodTakingInjections</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Injections may be taken on Saturday or Monday.
      Aries, Taurus. Cancer and Virgo are auspicious. The 8th house must be
      unoccupied. See that Mercury is free from affliction; as otherwise the
      pain wilt be severe and nervous weakness may set in.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Medical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>71</Id>
    <Name>GoodSellingForProfit</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Selling for Profit. - Let the Moon and Mercury be free from the
      conjunction or aspect of Mars. The Moon's situation in Taurus. Cancer
      or Pisces would greatly help the seller. Try to keep Mercury in a kendra
      from Lagna or at least in good aspect to Jupiter. Tuesday should be
      avoided. Monday, Wednesday and Thursday are the best. While Friday
      is unpropitious, Saturday is middling.
    </Description>
    <Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>72</Id>
    <Name>BavaKarana</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Bava is auspicious for starting works of permanent importance.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>73</Id>
    <Name>TaitulaKarana</Name>
    <Nature>Good</Nature>
    <Description>
      Thaithula is propitious for marriage
    </Description>
    <Tag>Marriage</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>74</Id>
    <Name>BhadraKarana</Name>
    <Nature>Bad</Nature>
    <Description>
      Bhadra is unfit for any good work but is eminently suitable for
      violent and cruel deeds.
    </Description>
    <Tag>General</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>75</Id>
    <Name>JanmaNakshatraRulling</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
      A day ruled by one's Janma Nakshatra is ordinarily held to be
      unfavourable for an election. But in regard to nuptials, sacrifices, first
      feeding, agriculture, upanayanam, coronation, buying lands, learning
      the alphabet, Janma Nakshatra is favourable without exception. But it is
      inauspicious for war, sexual union, shaving, taking medical treatment,
      travel and marriage. For a woman, Janma Nakshatra would be quite
      favourable for marriage.
    </Description>
    <Tag>Personal</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>76</Id>
    <Name>SunIsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>77</Id>
    <Name>MoonIsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>78</Id>
    <Name>MarsIsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>79</Id>
    <Name>MercuryIsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>80</Id>
    <Name>JupiterIsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>81</Id>
    <Name>VenusIsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>82</Id>
    <Name>SaturnIsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>83</Id>
    <Name>House1IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>84</Id>
    <Name>House2IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>85</Id>
    <Name>House3IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>86</Id>
    <Name>House4IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>87</Id>
    <Name>House5IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>88</Id>
    <Name>House6IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>89</Id>
    <Name>House7IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>90</Id>
    <Name>House8IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>91</Id>
    <Name>House9IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>92</Id>
    <Name>House10IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>93</Id>
    <Name>House11IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>
  <Event>
    <Id>94</Id>
    <Name>House12IsStrong</Name>
    <Nature>Neutral</Nature>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
  </Event>

</Root>