<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Root xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<!--This is the ULTIMATE DATA list for MUHURTHA Events-->
	<!--HOW THIS FILE USED BY VEDASTRO
	Data on what an event is set here by human coder.
	When "StaticGenerator" is run this file is proccessed to make static c# code.
	of what the-->


	<!--GHATAKA CHAKRA-->
	<Event>
		<Name>GhatakaMoonSign</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<ConditionDescription>If the ghataka element happens to be Moon</ConditionDescription>
		<Description>
			injury is on reputation,
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal, GhatakaChakra</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GhatakaTithiGroup</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<ConditionDescription>If the ghataka element happens to be Tithi or Nakshatra</ConditionDescription>
		<Description>
			the injury is more mental and emotional.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal, GhatakaChakra</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GhatakaWeekDay</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<ConditionDescription>If the ghataka element happens to be Weekday or the Lagna, </ConditionDescription>
		<Description>
			the injury is more physical
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal, GhatakaChakra</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GhatakaMoonConstellation</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<ConditionDescription>If the ghataka element happens to be Tithi or Nakshatra, </ConditionDescription>
		<Description>
			the injury is more mental and emotional.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal, GhatakaChakra</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GhatakaLagna</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<ConditionDescription>If the ghataka element happens to be Weekday or the Lagna, </ConditionDescription>
		<Description>
			the injury is more physical
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal, GhatakaChakra</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--PANCHA PAKSHI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>BirdRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Bird is at its highest activity of strength.
			Ruling, all his endeavours are crowned with success, he wins over others. He succeeds in interviews, he
			wins over the heart of his fiancé, he succeeds in any work which he starts during this time,
			his illness is cured if treatment is started during this time. At this stage; a girl attaining
			puberty (appearance of first period), lives in a highest standard of life happily throughout.
			Apart from the above
			this can be applied in the same way such as starting for a
			travel, going to see the higher-ups, performing marriage,
			starting education for the first time in life (putting to school
			first), accepting a new job, joining a new job, taking a new assignment or taking oath of allegiance for the post of Ministers,
			Head ofthe Departments etc. When once started, during the
			strongest ebb of vibrations or activities all these endeavours
			get succeeded
		</Description>
		<Tag>PanchaPakshi</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BirdEating</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The eating activity gets defeated by Ruling activity but
			wins over the remaining three viz.. Walking, Sleeping and
			Dying
		</Description>
		<Tag>PanchaPakshi</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BirdWalking</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Walking activity gets defeated by Ruling and Eating
			activity but wins over the other two activities viz.. Sleeping
			and Dying.
		</Description>
		<Tag>PanchaPakshi</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BirdSleeping</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>PanchaPakshi</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BirdDying</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>PanchaPakshi</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--TRAVEL-->
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodLunarDayForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			For journeys/travel the best lunar days are the 2nd, 3rd, 5th, 7th, 10th, 11th and 13th.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadLunarDayForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			For journeys/travel the 14th lunar day and Full and New Moon days should be avoided at any cost.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodConstellationForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			If a journey is undertaken in the following constellations, the person is
			supposed to return back early after satisfactorily completing his work:
			Mrigasira, Aswini, Pushya, Punarvasu, Hasta, Anuradha, Sravana,
			Moola, Dhanishta and Revati. It is better that the journey is commenced
			in the 2nd, 3rd or last quarter of the constellation. The first quarter may
			be avoided as far as possible.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadConstellationForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			No journey should be undertaken on days ruled by Krithika, Bharani.
			Aslesha. Visakha, Pubba, Poorvabhadra and Aridra. Of these, the
			following nakshatras may be deemed fit for travelling beyond the
			spheres of evil influence: - Krittika - 13 ghatis; Bharani - 7; Makha - 14;
			Pubba, Poorvashadha and Poorvabhadra - 16; Swati, Aslesha and
			Visakha - 14. In our humble experience, it is found that Bharani and
			Krithika should always be avoided while the other stars given in this
			paragraph, journeys can be undertaken in.
			We have to emphasize that Bharani and Krithika should be invariably
			rejected.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadWeekdayForTravelEast</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Do not travel towards the East on Saturday and Monday
			Provided the journey is timed to begin
			beyond 8 ghatis on Saturday and Monday, the
			above restriction does not hold good.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadWeekdayForTravelSouth</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Do not travel towards South on Thursday.
			Provided the journey is timed to begin
			beyond 22 ghatis on Thursday, the
			above restriction does not hold good.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadWeekdayForTravelWest</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Do not travel towards West on Sunday and Friday.
			Provided the journey is timed to begin
			beyond 15 ghatis on Friday and Sunday, the
			above restriction does not hold good.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadWeekdayForTravelNorth</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Do not travel towards North on Wednesday and Tuesday.
			Provided the journey is timed to begin
			beyond 12 ghatis on Tuesday and Wednesday, the
			above restriction does not hold good

			In our view, Tuesday must
			preferably be avoided.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodLagnaForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aries, Taurus, Cancer, Leo, Libra and Sagittarius are favorable signs
			for starting on a journey.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BestLagnaForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rising sign at the time of journey being one's Janma Rasi is highly
			favoured.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>WorstLagnaForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rising sign at the time of journey should never be the sign of one's Janma Lagna.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadLagnaForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Journey should not also be undertaken when the Lagna is the 5th, 7th
			or the 9th from one's Janma Lagna.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodPlanetsInLagnaForTravel</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Let Jupiter or Venus be well placed in Lagna at the time of starting. This
			makes the journey successful.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodMoonJupiterTravelYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Moon should be in the 3rd, 6th, 9th or 12th and Jupiter in a
			kendra from Lagna.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>FortifiedMoonTravelYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Start when the Moon is in Lagna fortified by the disposition of Jupiter
			or Venus in a kendra.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>StrongJupiterTravelYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter strong in Lagna and the Moon in any place other than the 8th
			would be a strong combination.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>EasyPeacefulTravelYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The journey will be easy and peaceful if the Moon be in the 7th and
			Venus and Mercury be in the 4th.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>NeutralizeBadTravelYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury in the 4th, Jupiter in the 2nd or 7th will neutralize all the
			other adverse influences.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>StrongBeneficsTravelYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Benefics dignified in kendras or trikonas act as powerful antidotes for
			all evils.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>IdealPlanetsTravelYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter in Lagna, malefics in Upachayas and Venus in any house
			other than the 7th would be an ideal combinations.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Travel</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--GENERAL-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AmritaSiddhaYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sunday to Saturday respectively coinciding with the constellations
			Hasta, Sravana, Aswini, Anuradha, Pushya, Revati and Rohini will give
			rise to Amita Siddha Yoga.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PanchangaSuddhi</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Panchanga Suddhi. - We have already said that a Panchanga
			consists of tithi, vara, nakshatra. yoga and karana. All these must be
			auspicious. In regard to lunar days, the 4th, 6th, 8th, 12th and 14th, full
			and new moon days should be avoided. In regard to vara, Thursday and
			Friday are held to be suitable for all works. Tuesday, is to be generally
			avoided except when it happens to be the 10th, 12th or 16th day of the
			child's birth when the child's Namakarana (baptising or giving name)
			may be performed. Of the several Nakshatras, Bharani and Krittika
			should be avoided for all auspicious works as these two are said to be
			presided o ver by the god of death (Yama) and the god of fire (Agni) respectively. In urgent cases if the Lagna could be fortified, the dosha
			due to nakshatra may get neutralised. The last parts of Aslesha,
			Jyeshta and Revati should also be avoided. Coming to the Yoga (vide
			page 12) the 6th (Atiganda). 9th (Soola). 10th (Ganda), 17th (Vyatipata)
			and 27th (Vydhruti) have deleterious effects upon events which are
			started or commenced under them. - The Karana chosen must be
			appropriate to the election in view. Thus Bava is auspicious for starting
			works of permanent importance while Thaithula is propitious for
			marriage. Bhadra is unfit for any good work but is eminently suitable for
			violent and cruel deeds. For getting initiation into kshudra mantras
			Sakuni Havana is propitious.
			Therefore, Panchanga Suddhi means a good lunar day, a beneficial
			weekday, an auspicious constellation, a good yoga and a fertilising
			Karana.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>UgraYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Any treatment commenced under Ugra yogas are supposed to prove
			successful. Ugra yogas arise when the 3rd (or 9th), 4th, 5th, 6th, 7th,
			9th, 10th, 12th (or 3rd) and 13th lunar days coincide respectively with
			Rohini, Uttara, Sravana, Mrigasira. Revats, Krittika, Pushva, Anuradha.
			Krittika (or Makha).
		</Description>
		<Tag>Medical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SuryaSankramana</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The 2nd great evil is Surya Sankramana or the
			solar ingress into different zodiacal signs. When the Sun is about to
			leave one sign and enter another there seem to occur certain
			disturbances in the organisation of the solar forces and such times are
			not recommended for any good work. On the contrary, they are held to
			be propitious for meditation, initiation into secret mantras and
			performance of certain religious rites which are held to purify not only
			the bodily electrical discharges but also the mental currents. Sixteen
			ghatis (6 hours 24 minutes) both before and after the entry of the Sun
			into a new sign should be rejected for all new works.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KarthariDosha</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Karthari means scissors. In an election, when two
			evil planets are placed on either side of the Lagna, the combination
			goes under the special name of Karthari Dosha and it should be
			rejected for good work particularly in regard to marriage.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ShashtashtaRiphagathaChandraDosha</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Shashtashta Riphagatha Chandra Dosha. - The Moon should
			invariably be avoided in the 6th, 8th and 12th houses from the Lagna
			rising in an election chart.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagrahaChandraDosha</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagraha Chandra Dosha. - The Moon's association (conjunction) with any other
			planet, benefic or malefic, should be avoided. This injunction is specially
			applicable in case of marriage.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>UdayasthaSuddhi</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Udayasta Suddhi. - The Lagna and the seventh should be strong.
			The Lagna should be occupied by its own lord and the Navamsa Lagna by its own lord or vice versa or lord of Lagna should aspect Navamsa
			Lagna and vice versa. Similarly the seventh and the lord of the seventh
			Bhava should be favourably disposed. The strength of Lagna and the
			seventh is necessary in all elections but especially so in regard to
			marriage.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SiddhaYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When a certain weekday coincides with a certain asterism and a certain
			lunar day, it becomes specialy auspicious for good work.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SakunaKarana</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>For getting initiations into mantras Sakini Karana is propitious</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BadNithyaYoga</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Coming to the Yoga the 6th (Atiganda). 9th (Soola). 10th (Ganda), 17th (Vyatipata)
			and 27th (Vydhruti) have deleterious effects upon events which are
			started or commenced under them.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>LagnaThyajya</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Even when the ascendant is strong, certain parts of it which go
			under the name of Lagna tyajya should be rejected. In Aries, Taurus, Sagittarius and Virgo, the first three degrees should be
			avoided as it is supposed to be in the nature of a serpent (bhujanga)
			and hence destructive. In regard to Pisces, Capricorn, Cancer and
			Scorpio, the last (three degrees) has to be avoided as it is supposed to
			be presided over by the evil force of Rahu. The middle half ghati (13°
			30' to 16° 30') should be rejected with regard to Gemini, Libra, Leo and
			Aquarius as it is ruled by an evil force termed Gridhra.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodPanchaka</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Panchaka (Five-Source Energy):

			For matters of ordinary importance
			such as interviewing superiors or going on short journeys, a favourable
			Tarabala will do and there is no need to consider the panchaka. But in
			regard to very important ceremonies such as marriage, nuptials, entry
			into new houses, etc., this should be carefully looked into.

			Five sources of planetary, stellar and zodiacal energies are involved. Take
			the number of the lunar day (from the 1st of the month), the number of
			the weekday, Sunday 1. etc.), the number of the constellation (from
			Aswini) and the number of the Lagna (from Aries). Add these together
			and divide the total by 9.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadPanchaka</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Panchaka (Five-Source Energy):

			For matters of ordinary importance such as interviewing superiors or going on short journeys,
			a favourable Tarabala will do and there is no need to consider the panchaka. But in
			regard to very important ceremonies such as marriage, nuptials, entry
			into new houses, etc., this should be carefully looked into.

			Five sources of planetary, stellar and zodiacal energies are involved. Take
			the number of the lunar day (from the 1st of the month), the number of
			the weekday, Sunday 1. etc.), the number of the constellation (from
			Aswini) and the number of the Lagna (from Aries). Add these together
			and divide the total by 9.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BhriguShatka</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The position of Venus in the 6th is injurious. This is
			especially so in regard to marriage. Even when Venus is exalted and
			associated with benefics, such a disposition is not approved.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>Kujasthama</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars should be avoided in the 8th house, as it
			indicates destruction of the object in view. In a marriage election chart.
			Mars in the 8th is unthinkable. Even if Mars is otherwise powerful, he
			should not occupy the 8th house.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodHairCutting</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Shaving may be had in the constellations
			of Pushya, Punarvasu, Rcvati, Hasta, Sravana,
			Dhanista, Mrignsira, Aswini, Chitta, Jyeshta,
			Satabliislia and Swati. 4th, Gth and 14th lunar
			days as also New Moon and Full Moon days
			arc not desirable. And solar and lunar eclipses.
		</Description>
		<Tag>HairNailCutting</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodNailCutting</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Avoid Fridays and Saturdays - the 8th, 9th, 14th lunar
			days as well as New and Full Moon days.
		</Description>
		<Tag>HairNailCutting</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>FixedConstellationRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rohini, Uttara, Uttarashadha and Uttarabhadra are supposed to be fixed
			constellations and they are favourable for coronations, laying the
			foundations of cities, sowing operations, planting trees and other
			permanent things.
		</Description>
		<Tag>RulingConstellation,General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>SoftConstellationRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Chitta, Anuradha, Mrigasira and Revati are soft constellations. They are
			good for wearing new apparel, learning dancing, music and fine arts,
			sexual union and performance of auspicious ceremonies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>RulingConstellation,General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>LightConstellationRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aswini, Pushya, Hasta and Abhijit are light constellations, and they can
			be selected for putting ornamentation, pleasures and sports,
			administering medicine, starting industries and undertaking travels.
		</Description>
		<Tag>RulingConstellation,General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>SharpConstellationRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Moola, Jyestha, Aridra and Aslesha are sharp in nature and they are
			favourable for incantations, invoking spirits, for imprisonment, murders,
			and separation of friends.
		</Description>
		<Tag>RulingConstellation,General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>MovableConstellationRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saravana, Dhanishta, Satabhisha, Punarvasu and Swati are movable
			stars and they are auspicious for acquiring vehicles, for gardening and
			for going on procession.
		</Description>
		<Tag>RulingConstellation,General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>DreadfulConstellationRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pubba, Poorvashadha and Poorvabhadra, Bharani and Makha are
			dreadful stars and they are suitable for nefarious schemes, poisoning,
			deceit, imprisonment, setting fire and other evil deeds.
		</Description>
		<Tag>RulingConstellation,General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>MixedConstellationRuling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Krittika and Visakha are mixed constellations and during their
			influences, works of day-to-day importance can be undertaken.
		</Description>
		<Tag>RulingConstellation,General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BadForStartingAllAgriculture</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			While beginning all agricultural operations, see that the 8th house is unoccupied.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>LagnaLordIsWeekdayLord</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Lagna owned by the planet who is lord of the weekday in question.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodLunarDayAgriculture</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			All odd lunar days except the 9th are good. All even tithis except the 2nd and 4th should be avoided.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BadLagnaForAllAgriculture</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini: Not favourable for any planting being a barren sign.
			Leo: Not good for any planting, especially bad for underground plants such as potato.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodYogaForAllAgriculture</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good yoga for all agriculture is formed when:
			1. A good lunar day for planting
			2. Lagna owned by the planet who is lord of the weekday
			3. Beginning all agricultural operations, see that the 8th house is unoccupied
			4. No malefic rising sign (Gemini and Leo)
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodAnySeedsSowing</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Any seeds can be sown on a day ruled by Hasta,
			Chitta, Swati, Makha, Pushyami, Uttara, Uttarashadha, Uttarabhadra,
			Rohini, Revati, Aswini, Moola or Anuradha provided the lunar day is
			also propitious. Choose a Lagna, owned by the planet who is lord of the
			weekday in question.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>Ekadashi</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			It is the 11th tithi. Special religious significance in Hindu tradition, usually it's observed by fasting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>NotAuspiciousDay</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Tuesday and Saturday should be avoided for all good and auspicious works.
			Tuesday is not evil after midday
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodPlanetsInLagna</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus, Mercury or Jupiter in the ascendant will completely destroy all other adverse influences.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingFloweringPlants</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting flowering plants when Virgo is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingGarlic</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting garlic when Aries is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingPeachAndOthers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting peach, plum, potatoes, radishes, onion sets and turnips when Taurus is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingTomatoesAndOthers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting beans, cabbage, corn, cucumber, lettuce, melons, pumpkins, tomatoes, cauliflower,
			water melons, and cereals when Cancer is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingGrains</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting wheat, rye, barley, rice and other field crops when Libra is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingOnionAndOthers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting garlic and onion seeds when Scorpio is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingPepperAndOthers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting Pepper and other spring crops and garlic when Sagittarius is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingPotatoAndOthers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting potato, radishes and turnips when Capricorn is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingGrainsAndOthers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting all black cereals and grains when Aquarius is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingPumpkinsAndOthers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting cucumbers, pumpkins, radishes, water-melons and carrots when Pisces is rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingTrees</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting trees in Rohini
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingSugarcane</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for planting sugarcane in Punarvasu
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingFlowerSeeds</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Seeds of flower plants, and fruit-bearing creepers should be sown in the asterisms of
			Mriyusira, Punarvasu, Hasta, Chitta, Swati, Anuradha and Revati
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingFruitTrees</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Seedlings of long-lived fruit trees when Jupiter is in Lagna on Thursday
			OR
			Fruit trees may be planted when Sagittarius and Pisces are rising on Thursday
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingFlowerTrees</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Seedlings of flower trees when Venus is in Lagna on Friday
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingFlowers</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Seedlings of flower sown when Mars is in Lagna on Tuesday
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForPlantingFlowerCuttings</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Flower seeds and cuttings may be sown when Taurus or Libra rising
			and general good time for planting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Agriculture</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodRullingConstellation</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pushya rulling is a constellation par excellence that could
			be universally employed for all purposes, excepting of course marriage
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BadRullingConstellation</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Certain constellations, apart from their being harmonious or otherwise disposed
			with reference to one's own Janma Nakshatra, should be avoided for
			certain specific purposes on account of their inherent evil natures. In
			fact, Bharani is condemned for all good work and it has to be
			scrupulously avoided for all good work.

			When a constellation like
			Bharani(beta Arietis) is held to be constitutionally unfit for certain types
			of elections; it means that the vibrations emanating from it are
			destructive in character

			Of the several Nakshatras, Bharani and Krittika
			should be avoided for all auspicious works as these two are said to be
			presided over by the god of death (Yama) and the god of fire (Agni)
			respectively. In urgent cases if the Lagna could be fortified, the dosha
			due to nakshatra may get neutralised. The last parts of Aslesha,
			Jyeshta and Revati should also be avoided.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodTakingInjections</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Injections may be taken on Saturday or Monday.
			Aries, Taurus. Cancer and Virgo are auspicious. The 8th house must be
			unoccupied. See that Mercury is free from affliction; as otherwise the
			pain wilt be severe and nervous weakness may set in.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Medical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodSellingForProfit</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Selling for Profit. - Let the Moon and Mercury be free from the
			conjunction or aspect of Mars. The Moon's situation in Taurus. Cancer
			or Pisces would greatly help the seller. Try to keep Mercury in a kendra
			from Lagna or at least in good aspect to Jupiter. Tuesday should be
			avoided. Monday, Wednesday and Thursday are the best. While Friday
			is unpropitious, Saturday is middling.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BavaKarana</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Bava is auspicious for starting works of permanent importance.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TaitulaKarana</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Thaithula is propitious for marriage
		</Description>
		<Tag>Marriage</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BhadraKarana</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Bhadra is unfit for any good work but is eminently suitable for
			violent and cruel deeds.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>JanmaNakshatraRulling</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			A day ruled by one's Janma Nakshatra is ordinarily held to be
			unfavourable for an election. But in regard to nuptials, sacrifices, first
			feeding, agriculture, upanayanam, coronation, buying lands, learning
			the alphabet, Janma Nakshatra is favourable without exception. But it is
			inauspicious for war, sexual union, shaving, taking medical treatment,
			travel and marriage. For a woman, Janma Nakshatra would be quite
			favourable for marriage.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--ASTRONOMICAL-->
	<Event>
		<Name>Yama1</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical,YamaNumber</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Yama2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical,YamaNumber</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Yama3</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical,YamaNumber</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Yama4</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical,YamaNumber</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Yama5</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical,YamaNumber</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunIsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonIsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>MarsIsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>MercuryIsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>JupiterIsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>VenusIsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>SaturnIsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House1IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House2IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House3IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House4IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House5IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House6IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House7IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House8IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House9IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House10IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House11IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>House12IsStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>BadForBuyingToolsUtensilsJewellery</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Buying Utensils, etc. Avoid the asterisms of Aslesha. Moola and Jyeshta. For buying tools, similarly avoid the 8th
			and 9th lunar days and New Moon.

			Buying Jewellery.
			As usual unfavourable lunar days and asterisms should be
			avoided.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForBuyingBrassVessels</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Buying Utensils, etc. -
			Place Jupiter in good aspect to the Moon while buying brass vessels.
			Avoid the asterisms of Aslesha. Moola and Jyeshta.
			For buying tools, similarly avoid the 8th
			and 9th lunar days and New Moon.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForBuyingCopperVessels</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Buying Utensils, etc. -
			Place Jupiter in good aspect to Mars when buying vessels of copper.
			Avoid the asterisms of Aslesha. Moola and Jyeshta.
			For buying tools, similarly avoid the 8th
			and 9th lunar days and New Moon.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForBuyingSteelIronVessels</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Buying Utensils, etc. -
			Place Jupiter in good aspect to Saturn if steel and iron.
			Avoid the asterisms of Aslesha. Moola and Jyeshta.
			For buying tools, similarly avoid the 8th
			and 9th lunar days and New Moon.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForBuyingSilverVessels</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Buying Utensils, etc. -
			Place Jupiter in good aspect to ascendant if of silver.
			Avoid the asterisms of Aslesha. Moola and Jyeshta.
			For buying tools, similarly avoid the 8th
			and 9th lunar days and New Moon.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodForBuyingJewellery</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Buying Jewellery. - The Sun and the Moon should be well situated and
			aspected. As usual unfavourable lunar days and asterisms should be
			avoided.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodPlanetsIn11th</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The mere presence of the Moon or the Sun in the 11th will act as an
			antidote for other evils obtaining in the horoscope.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodPlanetsInKendra</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter or Venus in a kendra (quadrant) and malefics in 3, 6 or 11
			will remove all the flaws arising on account of unfavourable weekday,
			constellation, lunar day and yoga.
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>Sunrise</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			It has been acknowledged
			that it is the moment at which the centre
			of the solar disc rises at the eastern horizon, that
			marks the sunrise at the particular place. It must
			also be noted that on account of the refraction
			of the solar rays, due to the various strata
			enveloping the earth, the Sun is not really at the
			horizon where he appears to be so but is really
			below the horizon by about a few minutes of
			arc (Rekha). But we can take the apparent time
			as almost correct and need not worry ourselves
			with the so called delicate correct time of rising.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>Sunset</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			It has been acknowledged
			that it is the moment at which the centre
			of the solar disc rises at the western horizon, that
			marks the sunset at the particular place. It must
			also be noted that on account of the refraction
			of the solar rays, due to the various strata
			enveloping the earth, the Sun is not really at the
			horizon where he appears to be so but is really
			below the horizon by about a few minutes of
			arc (Rekha). But we can take the apparent time
			as almost correct and need not worry ourselves
			with the so called delicate correct time of setting.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>Midday</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			This is marked when the centre of the Sun is exactly on the
			meridian of the place. The apparent noon is
			almost the same for all places.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Astronomical</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--CHANDRABALA-->
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodChandrabala</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			To be at its best, the Moon should not
			occupy in the election chart, a position that happens to
			represent the 6th, 8th or 12th from the persons Janma Rasi
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Chandrabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadChandrabala</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			To be at its best, the Moon should not
			occupy in the election chart, a position that happens to
			represent the 6th, 8th or 12th from the persons Janma Rasi

			Exceptions:
			Chandrashtama (8th) shows no evil when the Moon is waxing and
			occupies a benefic sign and a benefic Navamsa, or when there is
			Tarabala. The sting is lost when the Moon and the 8th lord are friends.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Chandrabala</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--TARABALA-->
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaJanmaStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Janma: danger to body
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the evil suggested holds good in full
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaJanmaMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Janma: danger to body
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be only fifty percent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaJanmaWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Janma: danger to body
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be almost negligible
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaSampatStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sampat: wealth and prosperity
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the good suggested holds good in full
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaSampatMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sampat: wealth and prosperity
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be only fifty percent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaSampatWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sampat: wealth and prosperity
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be almost negligible
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaVipatStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Vipat: dangers, losses and accidents
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the evil suggested holds good in full

			It is better to avoid Vipat and Naidhana stars
			for all important undertakings - long journeys, marriage, starting of an enterprise, etc.,
			even if such a star happens to fall in the 3rd-cycle, unless there are other counteracting factors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaVipatMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Vipat: dangers, losses and accidents
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be only fifty percent.

			It is better to avoid Vipat and Naidhana stars
			for all important undertakings - long journeys, marriage, starting of an enterprise, etc.,
			even if such a star happens to fall in the 3rd-cycle, unless there are other counteracting factors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaVipatWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Vipat: dangers, losses and accidents
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be almost negligible

			It is better to avoid Vipat and Naidhana stars
			for all important undertakings - long journeys, marriage, starting of an enterprise, etc.,
			even if such a star happens to fall in the 3rd-cycle, unless there are other counteracting factors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaKshemaStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Kshema: prosperity
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the good suggested holds good in full
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaKshemaMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Kshema: prosperity
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be only fifty percent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaKshemaWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Kshema: prosperity
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be almost negligible
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaPratyakStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pratyak: obstacles
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the evil suggested holds good in full
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaPratyakMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pratyak: obstacles
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be only fifty percent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaPratyakWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pratyak: obstacles
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be almost negligible
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaSadhanaStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sadhana: realisation of ambitions
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the good suggested holds good in full
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaSadhanaMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sadhana: realisation of ambitions
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be only fifty percent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaSadhanaWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sadhana: realisation of ambitions
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be almost negligible
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaNaidhanaStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Naidhana: dangers
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the evil suggested holds good in full

			It is better to avoid Vipat and Naidhana stars
			for all important undertakings - long journeys, marriage, starting of an enterprise, etc.,
			even if such a star happens to fall in the 3rd-cycle, unless there are other counteracting factors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaNaidhanaMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Naidhana: dangers
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be only fifty percent.

			It is better to avoid Vipat and Naidhana stars
			for all important undertakings - long journeys, marriage, starting of an enterprise, etc.,
			even if such a star happens to fall in the 3rd-cycle, unless there are other counteracting factors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaNaidhanaWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Naidhana: dangers
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the evil is said to be almost negligible

			It is better to avoid Vipat and Naidhana stars
			for all important undertakings - long journeys, marriage, starting of an enterprise, etc.,
			even if such a star happens to fall in the 3rd-cycle, unless there are other counteracting factors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaMitraStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mitra: good
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the good suggested holds good in full
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaMitraMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mitra: good
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be only fifty percent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaMitraWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mitra: good
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be almost negligible
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaParamaMitraStrong</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Parama Mitra: very favourable
			1st Paryaya or cycle : the good suggested holds good in full
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaParamaMitraMiddling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Parama Mitra: very favourable
			2nd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be only fifty percent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>TarabalaParamaMitraWeak</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Parama Mitra: very favourable
			3rd Paryaya or cycle : the good is said to be almost negligible
		</Description>
		<Tag>Personal,Tarabala</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Others-->
	<Event>

		<Name>Papashadvargas</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Papashadvargs : Malefics should not be strong in shadvargas in an election chart.
			This event idicates that malefics are strong in shadvargas
		</Description>
		<Tag>General</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Buying & Selling-->
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodMoonSignForSelling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Selling for Profit. - The Moon's situation in Taurus. Cancer
			or Pisces would greatly help the seller.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>

		<Name>GoodWeekdayForSelling</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Selling for Profit. - Monday, Wednesday and Thursday are the best.
		</Description>
		<Tag>BuyingSelling</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Gochara SUMMARY-->
	<Event>
		<Name>GocharaSummary</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Combination of all gochara occurring at time.
		</Description>
		<Tag>GocharaSummary</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Gochara Sun-->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>
				<Weight>2.2</Weight>
				<Nature>Bad</Nature>
			</Body>
			<Money>
				<Weight>2.2</Weight>
				<Nature>Bad</Nature>
			</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When the Sun traverses through the Rasi occupied by
			the Moon, the person suffers from loss of wealth, loss of
			prestige, sickness and will have many obstacles and aimless
			travels. Financial loss, discomfort, chest pain and aimless journey
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Money>Bad</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When he transits in the 2nd house, there will be loss
			of wealth, he will suffer deceit, he will have full of financial
			worries. Increase of expenditure, eye trouble, deceit and unhappiness
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Good</Mind>
			<Body>Good</Body>
			<Money>Good</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 3rd house there will be advent of money,
			happiness, relief from diseases, recognition from superiors,
			honours and courage. Increase of emoluments, freedom from sickness
			and destruction of enemies
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Money>Bad</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 4th house, there will be diseases,
			constant attacks from opponents, no peace of mind, pressure
			from creditors, and sorrow and misery. Quarrels with wife,
			unhappiness in conjugal life and the general ailments
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			The Sun transiting the 5th will cause mental agitation,
			ill-health, embarrassment and accidents. Increase of enemies and
			physical indisposition
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Good</Body>
			<Mind>Good</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			The Sun in the 6th gives rise to release from
			sorrows, worries and troubles, destruction of enemies and
			peace of mind. Success over enemies, joy and good health.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			The Sun transiting the 7th, produces wearisome
			travelling, colic and anal troubles, humiliation and
			sickness. Wearisome travelling, chest pain and stomach troubles.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 8th, Sun's progress gives rise to quarrels
			with friends, diseases, high blood pressure, royal and official
			displeasure. Misunderstandings with or separation from wife.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			The Sun's transit in the 9th house will cause to
			the native danger, humiliation, dependency, disappointment
			and separation. Accidents, stomach trouble, mental worry and
			opposition.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Good</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			One will accomplish his desire and plans,
			and success will attend on all kinds or undertakings when the
			Sun is in the 10th. Success in endeavors, honour and realisation
			of ambition
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Good</Mind>
			<Body>Good</Body>
			<Money>Good</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 11th, the passage of the Sun will
			confer on a person honour, health, wealth and success.
			Great success, respect, freedom from disease and prosperity.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When the Sun passes through the 12th house, there will be sorrow,
			creation of a situation which causes loss to everything,
			quarrels and ill-health.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Gochara Moon-->
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Money>Good</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When the Moon transits the sign occupied by her at the time of
			birth of a person, the native will get excellent food,
			bed and clothes. Good food, comforts and clothes
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Money>Bad</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When the Moon passes through the 2nd house,
			loss of respect and of money and obstacles in
			the way of success are to be predicted.
			Loss of respect, money and increase of obstacles.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Family>Good</Family>
			<Money>Good</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 3rd house, the native gets clothes,
			pleasure from wife and finance.
			Domestic happiness and access to money
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 4th, he becomes mentally uneasy.
			Loss of trust in others and lack of peace of mind.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 5th, suffers from humility, ill-health, pain of mind
			and other obstacles. Indisposition, grief and disappointment;
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Good</Mind>
			<Body>Good</Body>
			<Money>Good</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 6th, enjoys wealth, health, comfort, redemption from enemies.
			Happiness, success over enemies and good health.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Money>Good</Money>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			7th house, conveyances, good food and
			financial equilibrium. Respect from others and
			sudden influx of unexpected resources.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			The Moon transiting the 8th produces misery,
			ill-health and fear from unexpected sources.
			Apprehension, uneasiness and worry.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 9th from herself, pain of mind, chest pain,
			fatigue of body and the like are caused.
			Mental pain, stomach trouble and incarceration.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Good</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When the Moon passes through the 10th
			house, success will attend in every sphere of activity.
			Success, authority and position, realisation of ambition.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Money>Good</Money>
			<Family>Good</Family>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			In the 11th house, the person will enjoy prosperity,
			will get wealth and new friends. Prosperity, new friends and
			good income
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Body>Bad</Body>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When the Moon transits through the 12th sign.
			He suffers from accidents and injuries.
			Injuries due to fall from vehicles and
			increased expenditure.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Gochara Mars-->
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Mind>Bad</Mind>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			When Mars passes through tbe sign occupied by the Moon
			at the time of birth of a person, be will suffer from troubles.
			Troubles from various sources and bodily affliction.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 2nd house from the Moon displeasure of king, and
			suffering from quarrels, from enemies and disgrace is indicated.
			There will be fear from thieves and the body will be
			afflicted with bilious and windy complaints.
			Trouble from the Government, frequent quarrels with enemies,
			disease, accidents, bilious and windy complaints
			and loss by theft.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars transiting the 3rd gives rise to gain of objects,
			pleasure from children, good health, access to riches
			and new clothes. Benefits through auspicious characters,
			financial improvement and acquisition of woolen articles
			and also authority.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 4th sign, Mars produces evil results such as fever,
			digestive troubles, blood discharges and depravity of character.
			Fever, stomachache, piles and blood discharges and
			frequent trouble from ailments.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Enemies will increase, fresh diseases will make their appearance
			and mental peace will be completely absent when Mars passes through
			the 5th house. Trouble from enemies, illness, misunderstandings
			with children and loss of physical energy.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 6th house, relief from troubles, worries
			and ill-health should be predicted; he leads an independent
			life, obtains riches and becomes pretty cheerful.
			Success over enemies, termination of strife in the family,
			and acquisition of self-confidence
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When transiting the 7th, tbe native quarrels with wife or husband,
			eye troubles, stomach-ache, indigestion, etc., are also likely
			to be felt. Frequent quarrels with wife, eye trouble and stomachache.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars transiting in the 8th produces quite unfavorable
			effects, such as discharging of blood, loss of
			wealth, disgrace and mental worry.
			Loss of blood from piles and anemia and loss of wealth and name.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars transiting in the 9th produces quite unfavorable
			effects, such as discharging of blood, loss of
			wealth, disgrace and mental worry.In addition,
			the subject becomes extremely weak.
			Suffering from insults, heavy expenditure and weakness
			due to ill-health.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			His transiting the 10th produces quite favourable results.
			Amounts due will be realised. Success will attend on his ventures.
			Business will improve. Acquisition of money from unexpected source.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			His transiting the 11th produces quite favourable results.
			Amounts due will be realised. Success will attend on his ventures.
			Business will improve. Fame, reputation and authority
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 12th house, however,he will suffer from various expenses,
			troubles, diseases of the eye, pinpricks from an angry wife,
			from bilious complaints and various other worries.
			Unforeseen expenses, quarrels with wife, eye disease and
			bilious affections
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Gochara Mercury-->
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Mercury passes through the sign occupied by the
			Moon at time of birth of a person, such person will suffer
			loss of wealth caused by the advice of wicked men, by talebearers,
			by imprisonment and quarrels. He will, besides,
			receive disagreeable intelligence when in his journey.
			Loss of money due to advice by wicked men, worry due to
			association with tale-bearers, quarrels,
			imprisonment and disagreeable news while travelling
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Mercury passes through the 2nd house, the person will suffer
			disgrace but gains success and wealth. Disgrace, ill-treatment
			from relatives but acquisition of success and wealth
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When he passes through tbe 3rd house, the subject will get friends,
			will be afraid of troubles from the king and from his enemies, he
			will quit his place due to his wicked deeds. New friends,
			but anticipation of trouble from government and enemies,
			aimless roaming about due to misdeeds
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Mercury passes through the 4th house, the person's kinsmen and
			family will increase and there will be much gain.
			Prosperity for relatives and family members,
			addition to family and gain of money.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 5th house, the person will quarrel with his wife and
			sons and will not enjoy the company of an excellent wife.
			Quarrels with wife and children.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 6th house,the person will be liked by all and will gain renown.
			Gain of renown, success and popularity.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 7th house, the person's appearance becomes less bright and
			there will be quarrels. Bloodlessness, quarrels and mental uneasiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Mercury passes through the 8th house, the person will get sons,
			success, clothes and wealth and will become happy and powerful.
			Birth of an issue, success, happiness and acquisition of new
			articles.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When he passes through the 9th house from the Moon,
			the person will meet with obstacles in his work.
			Obstacles and mental worry.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 10th house, the person's enemies
			will meet with ruin and the person will get wealth, will enjoy
			the company of his wife and will be dressed in the flannel.
			Defeat of enemies, acquisition of money,
			happiness with wife and agreeable company.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Mercury passes through the 11th house from the Moon,
			the person will get wealth, comfort, sons, women, friends and
			conveyance and will be happy and will receive good intelligence.
			Acquisition of wealth; birth of a son and happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 12th, the person will suffer disgrace from his
			enemies, will suffer from diseases and will not enjoy the
			company of a good wife. Disgrace from enemies, disease
			and domestic disharmony.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Gochara Jupiter-->
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the sign occupied by the
			Moon at the time of birth of a person, such person will lose
			his wealth and intelligence, will quit his place and will suffer
			from many quarrels. Loss of money and intelligence,
			aimless roaming about and frequent quarrels.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 2nd
			house from the Moon, the person will have no enemies and
			will enjoy wealth and women. Happiness, domestic harmony and success
			over enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through
			the 3rd house from the Moon, the person will quit his place
			and will meet with obstacles in his work.
			Moving about from place to place, obstacles to
			own work and loss of position.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 4th house from the Moon,
			the person will suffer from troubles caused by his kinsmen,
			will become patient and resigned and will delight in nothing.
			Troubles from relatives, development of a sense of resignation
			to the inevitable.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 5th house from the Moon,
			the person will get servants, prosperity, sons, elephants,
			houses, bullocks, gold, women, clothes, gems and good qualities.
			Acquisition of servants, birth of a son, general
			prosperity, addition of property and development
			of good qualities.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 6th house from the Moon,
			the person will be so much afflicted at heart that he will take
			no delight in the agreeable faces of beautiful women,
			in the music of the peacock and the cuckoo and in houses made
			pleasant by the frolic of children playing like the young of the deer.
			Affliction of mind, friends turning enemies and
			indifferent to good things.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 7th house from the Moon, the
			person will enjoy good bed, the company of an excellent
			woman, wealth, good meals, flowers, conveyance and the like
			and be will be of good speech and intelligence.
			Happiness, erotic pleasure, good income,
			purchase of a conveyance and graceful speech
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 8th house from the Moon,
			the person will suffer from imprisonment, diseases, heavy grief,
			the fatigue of journey and serious illness.
			Imprisonment, disease, heavy grief and
			serious illness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through
			the 9th house from the Moon, the person will become efficient
			at work and influential and he will get sons, success in work,
			wealth and gain. Influential, birth of an issue,
			success in work and acquisition of wealth from an
			unexpected source.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 10th
			house from the Moon, the person will quit his place and
			suffer loss of health and wealth.
			Destruction of position, loss of money and health and aimless
			roaming about.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 11th house, the person will
			return to his country and will recover his health and wealth.
			Reinstatement in former position, and recovery of health.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Jupiter passes through the 12th house, the person will
			suffer grief in his return journey.
			Fall from ideals and right conduct and increase of
			grief.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Gochara Venus-->
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the sign occupied by the
			Moon at the time of birth of a person, such a person will
			enjoy excellent perfumes, flowers, clothes, houses, bed, meals
			and women. Acquisition of comforts for pleasure, and a happy life.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 2nd house from
			the Moon, the person will get sons, wealth, grain and presents
			from the king; will have a prosperous family, will enjoy
			flowers and gems and will be of bright appearance.
			Acquisition of money and gifts, birth of an issue and erotic
			pleasure.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 3rd house from the Moon, the
			person will become influential, wealthy and respectable and
			will get clothes. His enemies will meet with ruin.
			Influence, wealth and respect.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 4th house, the person will get
			friends and will become greatly powerful.
			Disgrace to enemies and general prosperity.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 5th house, the person will be happy, will get
			kinsmen, sons, wealth and friends and will not suffer defeat
			by the enemy. Renewal of contact with friends, increase of
			reputation, influence and power.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 6th house
			from the Moon, the person will suffer disgrace, will be
			afflicted with diseases and will be exposed to danger.
			General happiness, extension of business, birth of an
			issue and good income.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 7th house, the person will suffer
			injuries through women. Humiliation, disease and danger.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 8th house from the Moon,
			the person will get houses, articles of
			lacquer and beautiful women. Injuries and trouble from women
			and mental worry.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 9th house from the Moon, the person will become
			virtuous, happy and wealthy and he will get plenty or clothes.
			Acquisition of a new house, articles of luxury and wife
			if not married.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 10th house from the Moon,
			the person will suffer disgrace and will also suffer quarrels.
			Increase of virtue, happiness, wealth and
			performance of religious acts.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 11th house from the Moon,
			the person will get wealth of his friends and will also get
			perfumes and clothes. Quarrels and disgrace.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Venus passes through the 12th house, the person will get
			very few clothes. Acquisition of new friends, money,
			perfumes and clothes.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Gochara Saturn-->
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the sign occupied by the
			Moon at the time of his birth, such person will suffer from
			poison and from fire, will quit his kinsmen, will suffer from
			imprisonment and torture, will travel to foreign lands and
			live with his friend there, will suffer miseries, loss of wealth
			and or sons, will suffer also from the fatigues of foot journey
			and from humiliation. Fear from poison or fire, of
			friends and family members, fear of incarceration,
			travel to foreign lands, loss of money and
			near relatives, separation from kith and kin and
			suffering from insults.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 2nd
			house from the Moon, the person will suffer from loss of
			beauty and comfort, will become weak and will get wealth
			from other men but will not enjoy this wealth long.
			Emaciated physical appearance, loss of comfort,
			acquisition but not enjoyment of wealth
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 3rd house from the Moon, the
			person will get wealth, servants, articles of enjoyment,
			camels, buffaloes, elephants, asses and horses. He will
			become influential, happy, free from disease and will become
			greatly powerful and will defeat his enemies in fight.
			Increase of wealth and other comforts, good health,
			general happiness and disappearance of enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 4th house from the Moon, the
			person will be separated from his friends, wealth, and wife
			and ever suspecting evil in everything, will never feel happy.
			Separation from friends and family members, suspicious
			nature, crooked behaviour and wicked acts.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 5th house from the Moon,
			the person will be separated from his sons and wealth and
			will suffer from quarrels. Separation from sons, loss of money
			and frequent quarrels.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the
			6th house from the Moon, the person will be freed from his
			enemies and diseases and will enjoy the company of women.
			Freedom from enemies and diseases association with fair sex.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 7th or 8th house from the
			Moon, the person will be separated from his wife and sons,
			will travel on foot in a pitiable condition.
			Separation from wife and children and aimless roaming about.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 7th or 8th house from the
			Moon, the person will be separated from his wife and sons,
			will travel on foot in a pitiable condition.
			Indulgence in mean activities and bereft of happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When he passes through the 9th house,
			the person will be separated from his wife and sons,
			will travel on foot in a pitiable condition.
			Besides that, suffer from hatred, chest pain, imprisonment and in
			consequence will not properly observe the daily duties.
			Indulgence in mean activities and bereft of happiness.
			Suffers from hatred, heart trouble and even imprisonment.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 10th house, the person will get
			work and will suffer loss of wealth, learning and fame.
			Gets new avocation, but loses money and fame.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 11th house from the Moon, the
			person will become cruel and will get women and wealth.
			Frequent loss of temper but acquisition of wealth through wrong means.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Saturn passes through the 12th house from the Moon,
			the person will suffer from much grief. Grief, series of miseries,
			ill-health and general affliction.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Gochara Rahu-->
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the sign occupied by the
			Moon at the time of his birth, such person will suffer from
			poison and from fire, will quit his kinsmen, will suffer from
			imprisonment and torture, will travel to foreign lands and
			live with his friend there, will suffer miseries, loss of wealth
			and or sons, will suffer also from the fatigues of foot journey
			and from humiliation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 2nd
			house from the Moon, the person will suffer from loss of
			beauty and comfort, will become weak and will get wealth
			from other men but will not enjoy this wealth long.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 3rd house from the Moon, the
			person will get wealth, servants, articles of enjoyment,
			camels, buffaloes, elephants, asses and horses. He will
			become influential, happy, free from disease and will become
			greatly powerful and will defeat his enemies in fight.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 4th house from the Moon, the
			person will be separated from his friends, wealth, and wife
			and ever suspecting evil in everything, will never feel happy.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 5th house from the Moon,
			the person will be separated from his sons and wealth and
			will suffer from quarrels.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the
			6th house from the Moon, the person will be freed from his
			enemies and diseases and will enjoy the company of women.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 7th or 8th house from the
			Moon, the person will be separated from his wife and sons,
			will travel on foot in a pitiable condition.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 7th or 8th house from the
			Moon, the person will be separated from his wife and sons,
			will travel on foot in a pitiable condition.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When he passes through the 9th house,
			the person will be separated from his wife and sons,
			will travel on foot in a pitiable condition.
			Besides that, suffer from hatred, chest pain, imprisonment and in
			consequence will not properly observe the daily duties.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 10th house, the person will get
			work and will suffer loss of wealth, learning and fame.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 11th house from the Moon, the
			person will become cruel and will get women and wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Rahu passes through the 12th house from the Moon,
			the person will suffer from much grief.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Gochara Ketu-->
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Ketu passes through tbe sign occupied by the Moon
			at the time of birth of a person, be will suffer from troubles.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 2nd house from the Moon displeasure of king, and
			suffering from quarrels, from enemies and disgrace is indicated.
			There will be fear from thieves and the body will be
			afflicted with bilious and windy complaints.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse3</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu transiting the 3rd gives rise to gain of objects,
			pleasure from children, good health, access to riches
			and new clothes.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse4</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 4th sign, Ketu produces evil results such as fever,
			digestive troubles, blood discharges and depravity of character.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse5</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Enemies will increase, fresh diseases will make their appearance
			and mental peace will be completely absent when Ketu passes through
			the 5th house.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse6</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 6th house, relief from troubles, worries
			and ill-health should be predicted; he leads an independent
			life, obtains riches and becomes pretty cheerful.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse7</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			When transiting the 7th, tbe native quarrels with wife or husband,
			eye troubles, stomach-ache, indigestion, etc., are also likely
			to be felt.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse8</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu transiting in the 8th produces quite unfavorable
			effects, such as discharging of blood, loss of
			wealth, disgrace and mental worry.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse9</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu transiting in the 9th produces quite unfavorable
			effects, such as discharging of blood, loss of
			wealth, disgrace and mental worry.In addition,
			the subject becomes extremely weak.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse10</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			His transiting the 10th produces quite favourable results.
			Amounts due will be realised. Success will attend on his ventures.
			Business will improve.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse11</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			His transiting the 11th produces quite favourable results.
			Amounts due will be realised. Success will attend on his ventures.
			Business will improve.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuGocharaInHouse12</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			In the 12th house, however,he will suffer from various expenses,
			troubles, diseases of the eye, pinpricks from an angry wife,
			from bilious complaints and various other worries.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Gochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--ASHTAKVARGA GOCHARA : EFFECTS OF GOCHARA BASED SOLELY ON BINDU-->
	<!--Sun -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit8Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>wealth and prosperity and royal favour</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit7Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>welfare, happiness and pomp</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit6Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>rising power</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit5Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>wealth</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit4Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>both good and bad will be equal</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit3Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>fatigue through journey</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit2Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>sinful actions</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit1Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>severe sickness</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunTransit0Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>death</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Moon -->
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit8Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>happiness,prosperity and help from relatives</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit7Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>gain of clothes, agreeable food and gain of perfumes</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit6Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>study of Mantras and association with religious heads</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit5Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>courage and mental satisfaction</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit4Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>misery and ill-health</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit3Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>quarrels with relations</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit2Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>quarrels brought about by one's wife and one's wealth</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit1Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>irreparable losses</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonTransit0Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>sorrow and extreme panic</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Mars -->
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit8Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			gain of landed property and moneys, acquisition
			of a house and victory
		</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit7Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>prosperity through brothers</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit6Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>favour through kings</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit5Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>pleasing experiences</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit4Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>good and bad in equal proportion</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit3Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>separation from brothers and women</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit2Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>quarrels due to wife and wealth</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit1Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>disease, as smallpox, etc.</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsTransit0Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>disease in the stomach, fits and exhaustion</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Mercury -->
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit8Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>respect from rulers</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit7Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>increase of wealth and learning</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit6Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>success attending all efforts</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit5Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>reconciliation with relation</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit4Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>want of spirit in everything</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit3Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>anxiety through disturbed thoughts</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit2Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>diseases caused by mental worry</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit1Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>imprisonment by force and unexpected calamities</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryTransit0Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>unexpected loss of everytime and consequent mental worries</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Jupiter -->
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit8Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>sovereignty, ownership and kingly prosperity</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit7Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>gain of wealth and happiness</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit6Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>gain of clothes, vehicles and gold</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit5Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>ruin to enemies, accomplishment of desired objects</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit4Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>gain and loss in equal measure</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit3Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>nervous debility and ear diseases</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit2Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>royal frowns</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit1Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>loss of wealth and relations</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterTransit0Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>derangement of the mind, loss of wealth and children</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Venus -->
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit8Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			comfort from good clothes, women, flowers and
			wholesome food
		</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit7Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>gain of ornaments and pearls</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit6Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>happiness from agreeable wife</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit5Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>meeting with friends</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit4Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>equal dose of good and bad</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit3Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>quarrel with the people of the locality and relatives</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit2Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>diseases and dismissal from service</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit1Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>fear from water and poison</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusTransit0Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>all sorts of calamities</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Saturn -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit8Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			acquisition of administrative control over a
			village or town
		</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit7Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>acquisition of servants and domestic animals</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit6Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>popularity with thieves, hill tribes and army chief</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit5Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>gain of grain</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit4Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>good and bad equal</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit3Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>loss of wealth, servants, women and happiness</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit2Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>imprisonment, fear and disease</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit1Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>dirty fallen life</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnTransit0Bindu</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>ill-luck in everything</Description>
		<Tag>AshtakvargaGochara</Tag>
	</Event>



	<!--DASA-->

	<!--Sun Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Money>Good</Money>
			<Travel>Good</Travel>
			<Family>Bad</Family>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			The Dasa of the Sun in Aries in deep exaltation.- Sudden
			gains in cattle and wealth, much traveling in eastern
			countries, residence in foreign countries, quarrels among
			friends and relations, pleasure trips and picnic parties and
			company of beautiful women.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<SpecializedSummary>
			<Money>Good</Money>
			<Family>Good</Family>
		</SpecializedSummary>
		<Description>
			Taurus - Increase in landed properties, fame among relations
			and friends, cultivation of love and reverence for holy people
			and saints.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Much wealth, education, inclination
			to interest oneself in music and such other fine arts, and
			generally happy and cheerful.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Political success,
			always gay and happy, traveling in foreign countries and
			increase in lands, houses and wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Respect from
			kings and noble personages, righteous conduct, birth of
			children and respect among children.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Suffering off
			and on from physical complaints, loss of cattle, wealth and
			house and misunderstandings with close relatives and friends.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Reduced to poverty, troubled by enemies, failure in
			undertakings, death of brothers and friends and miserable
			and complicated life.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Starting new schemes and
			enterprises, realization of many ambitious things, travelling
			in hilly tracts and countries.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Happiness, success in undertakings, good health, destruction of enemies, satisfaction
			in every way.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - A wandering life, loss of
			patrimony, self-respect and good name, misunderstanding
			among his own people.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Mental worries, loss or
			illness to wife, loss of property and wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesSunPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Gains
			in wealth, auspicious celebrations, respect among relations,
			increase in family members and smooth sailing in every way.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Moon Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Moon in Aries - Physical and mental happiness,
			gains in wealth and perfect contentment.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - Increase
			in fame and name, collection of enormous wealth, mental and
			physical happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Progress in education and
			acquiring of much immovable and movable properties.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Addition in wealth, success in litigation, unexpected findings
			of treasure, travels.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Progress in education, much gains
			from unexpected sources.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Death of serious illness to
			mother, worries from enemies and swindlers, mental and
			physical restlessness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Gains in wealth, increase in
			friends, visits to holy places and shrines, realisation of
			schemes and destruction of enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Fear from
			political heads, destruction of relatives, disappointments in
			every respect, loss of wealth, liberty and honor at risk and
			much mental uneasiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Domestic happiness and felicity, celebration of happy functions, accumulation of
			wealth and undisturbed progress of normal private affairs.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Increase in lands and houses and wealth, success
			in every new enterprise, pilgrimages to holy places and success
			in litigation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Destruction of property, fear from
			political authorities, mental worries from enemies, misunderstandings
			among relatives and friends.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesMoonPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Taking
			charges of fresh office, reciting religious texts and moral codes
			and easy access to anything coveted without effort.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Mars Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aries - Acquisition of wealth, increase in reputation
			and respect, much gain.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - Destruction of
			enemies, success in all struggles, respect from elders and rulers
			and good produce from lands.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Access to great
			wealth, precious· stones and me~ agricultural success,
			general success in all undertakings.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Danger from
			enemies, of honour and reputation, domestic disharmony and
			misunderstandings among brothers or close relatives.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Happy
			and successful all through the period of 7 years, taste
			in fine arts and material gains through them, increase of income
			from house and lands.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Beneficial results, successful
			termination of educational pursuits, ability to address
			meetings and deliver lectures, and happiness from relatives
			and friends.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Most miserable life, misunderstandings
			with cousins and brothers, death of wife and children, loss of
			wealth and grains and mortgaging of landed property.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Increase in wealth, good earnings, friendship and intimacy with exalted personages,
			love for own people, always happy and active.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Earnings from political or royal
			sources, courting their friendships, destruction of enemies and
			realisation of all hopes and desires.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Success in
			battles and respect for military skill, gains from quadrupeds
			and increase in wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Great hardships and
			difficulties, misunderstandings with rulers and the immediate
			superiors in office, unpleasant relations with mother and
			servants.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesMarsPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Much wealth, general success and
			happiness. bumper crops in lands, prosperity and acquisition
			of house and business, respect as a learned man, great reputation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Rahu Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu In Aries - Auspicious celebrations in the house,
			recitations of sacred texts, acquisition of tracts of land,
			perfect domestic happiness, respect from rulers and a life of
			harmony in every respect.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - Pilgrimages to shrines
			and holy places, increase in philosophical knowledge, entertainments,
			gains from cattle and dealings with quadrupeds.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Multiplication of enemies, always peevish and short tempered,
			fear from police and magistrates, sickness to wife
			and family, misunderstandings and disfavour.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Serving the suffering, humanitarian propaganda, zeal and
			enthusiasm for national service, gains and increase in wealth,
			riches and honour and great reputation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Fear of imprisonment of fraud and deception or misappropriation or
			political offenses, destruction of property and mental worries
			distractions.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Gain in wealth, general prosperity and
			success, acquisition of new lands, elevation to exalted positions,
			respect for learning, sexual happiness and domestic
			harmony, birth of children and sudden access to much wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Destruction of property, loss of wealth, waste of
			agricultural products, loss of position, fear of imprisonment,
			residence in foreign countries-rather in exile, many miseries,
			hardships, business failure, litigation troubles and physical
			and mental sufferings.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Rahu is debilitated here
			and as such, causes great havoc to the native. The results in
			Rahu's Dasa will be :-abortion, loss of children, inclination
			to bid farewell to moral aspect of life, failure in business
			enterprises and mental discontentment.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Acquisition
			of wealth, sudden and unexpected gain without effort,
			great success in any undertakings, loss of near and dear
			relatives and mental unrest.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Sudden promotions
			to higher positions, recognition of one's merits by the State
			and rulers, marriage festivities at home, increase of wealth
			and general prosperity.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Orphanage, disappointments,
			mental derangement and affection, sorrowful news,
			loss of wife or children, premature death and mean instincts.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesRahuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Great fear in life from thieves, swindlers and such
			people, inclination to matrimonial alliance, progress of education,
			some gains, ill health and mental uneasiness. Rahu
			in Pisces gives mixed results - his position, viz., whether he is
			in a friendly or unfriendly sign, in the house of loss or gain,
			wife or children, etc., should be correctly determined.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Jupiter Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter in Aries - Acquisition of landed property, general
			prosperity and success in all undertakings and litigations,
			elevation to a responsible office or appointment as a trustee
			and great respect from his or her own people.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - If a king or a president - access to new territories, fresh treaties
			and pacts, if an ordinary person - acquisition of wealth, establishment
			of business on a firm foundation, gains in trade
			and agriculture, increase in lands and cattle, respect from friends and foes.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Death of wife if married or
			sweet heart, loss of children, brothers and cousins, deportation,
			fear from rulers and mental uneasiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Jupiter is exalted here and gives all beneficial results such as much
			political success, promotions, exalted positions, humanitarian
			work, national service, acquisition of wealth from unexpected
			sources and without efforts, journalistic success, minister of
			education or lands and perfect harmony in domestic life.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Respect from rulers, gain of lands, much agricultural
			produce, and realisation of one's own desires and ambitions.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Residence in foreign countries, destruction of wife
			and property, loss of wealth, misunderstandings among relatives,
			strife, body ill-health and symptoms of nervous
			troubles and diseases.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Residence in desolate places,
			dissolute and shameful life, active part in perverted social
			reform, selfish interests, great and unbearable difficulties and
			troubles, tendency to create factions in societies and families.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Mental calm and happiness, acquisition of new
			lands and estates, undisturbed progress and religious worship
			and philosophical discourses and triumph of spiritual influences
			over sensual passions, reputation at stake if aspected by
			malefics.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Many sons, much wealth, success in
			every undertaking, increase in relations and family members.
			widespread fame and perfect happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Death or
			illness of children, wife always ill, loss of property, reputation
			and self-respect, irreligious acts, sacrilegious attacks upon
			sacred institutions, predominance of mean motives, liable to
			prosecution and the upspringing of numerous enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Consumption and fear from wild beasts, animals,
			bad luck, many hardships and loss of wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesJupiterPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Much
			fame throughout this long period of 16 years, high education
			and gt1in from exhibition of knowledge, acquisition of
			property and general success and happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Saturn Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn In Aries - The worst period in a man's career,
			unexpected losses, disappointments in every undertaking, misunderstandings
			among relatives and friends and increase in the
			number of enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - Success and gains in agricultural
			operations, much prosperity to the cattle and other domestic
			animals, great income, and access to things desired.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Recognition of his services, great humanitarian work, profits
			in speculations and trade, respect from rulers, political
			success, reputation, fame and much general happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Miseries and calamities, family strife, increase of
			enemies, trouble from relatives and physical diseases and mental
			affliction.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - A period of uneasiness, distrust, disappointments
			and unrest, misappropriation of money and consequent
			prosecution if Saturn is afflicted powerfully, hatred by all and
			courting death as a source of relief from mental worries.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Elevation to exalted positions, royal favour, business
			success and establishment of fame and reputation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Travelling in countries inhabited by Christians and Moslems,
			establishment of fresh branches if proprietor of a business
			concern, acceptance of invitations for public lectures and
			great honour and respect throughout the long period of 19 years
			and perfect domestic happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Odium of superiors,
			disliked and hated by all, loss or prestige, self-respect and
			fame and destruction and damage to property and possessions.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Inclination to study philosophical and religious
			treatises and success in such studies, auspicious occasions like
			marriage ceremonies, etc., at home and happiness and mental
			peace throughout.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Increase in lands, gains in
			wealth and business, friendship with great and illustrious
			personages.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Great travelling in Western countries,
			success in litigation, mental happiness and acquisition of
			wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesSaturnPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Pilgrimage to sacred shrines and holy
			places, indifference towards sectarian restrictions and observances,
			sorrows, misery and unrest.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Mercury Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury in Aries - Marriage, performance of religious and
			social work, charity, increase in religiousness and intelligence,
			favour of rulers, gains from cultivation. cattle, precious
			stones and conveyances and happiness through these.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - Great happiness, sexual contact with beautiful young
			women, getting titles and name, ornaments and authority over
			men, acquaintance of sweet girls and their company and
			practice of music and kindred sciences.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Access to
			great intellectual treasures, increase in knowledge, successful
			termination of educational career, acquisition of fame and
			wealth, happiness from wife and children, marriage ceremonies
			and recitation of sacred scriptures.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Degradation,
			change of residence, fines and imprisonments, penalties.
			confinement in chains, hatred of relations, loss of lands.
			failure of crops and comity with all.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Good courage
			and elevation, travelling in hilly and mountainous tracts, acquisition of
			wealth from various countries, progress in
			knowledge, expeditions to mountains, caves and similar
			places, marriage and great reputation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - The most
			auspicious and happy period of life, favour of kings, admirers
			and royal courts and great success in them, undisturbed
			health, marriage in the house, increase in intelligence, religiousness,
			charitable foundings, and unexpected gains.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Great works published in the native's name, favour of
			wealthy and educated people without effort, and leadership
			over men.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Loss or wife, children, riches, mental
			troubles, losses from merchandise, great hatred of people and
			relations and loss of reputation and power.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Success
			in education, meeting with learned and religious
			people, worship of holy men, virtuous and charitable deeds,
			travelling in Eastern countries, inclination for marital enterprises
			and great exhilaration.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Success in trade,
			inception of new business-like trades in tanneries, leather
			goods, glassware, etc., recitation of religious scriptures. Godly
			contemplations, patronage of kings, destruction of foes and
			enemies and general success in life.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Acquisition
			of paraphernalia, access to good and much wealth, indulging
			in a pleasurely life and good fame and name.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesMercuryPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Trouble
			from thieves, dysentery, destruction of relations, litigation,
			quarrels with relatives, mental derangement, nervous breakdown
			and failure in attempts.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Ketu Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu in Aries - Disgrace, troubles from relatives, loss of
			property, cattle and other domestic animals, constant travels
			in Eastern countries, great hardship, sudden quarrels, loss of
			mother and wife or their serious sickness, want of prudence
			and capacity in private matters.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - Many dangers,
			death of wife, acquisition of wealth through evil ways and
			means, sexual sorrows, visits to sacred shrines and holy
			waters, inclination to religious study and success in it,
			compunction and in the end appeasing sins by resort to foul
			stratagems.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Good health, happiness, elevation to responsible
			and exalted positions, rounding of sacred institutions,
			good food, advent of relations and in later years venereal
			troubles, death of near relation and loss of reputation and
			self-respect.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Many dangers, disturbances from his
			place and a period of exile, serious sickness to wife, parents
			or children, and if badly afflicted, their death, quarrels with
			friends, initiation into the mysteries of philosophical knowledge.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Increase of lands, cultivation. progress in education,
			heated debates and discussions on philosophical and
			scientific subjects with great scholars and eminent people,
			attracted by females and company with them, travels in
			mountainous tracts and billy countries to spread any righteous
			cause, and treated to great musical entertainment.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Fear from fires, weapons and poisonous gases, beasts and reptiles,
			destruction of dear lives, properties and self-respect,
			unrighteous acts and nasty venereal complaints.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Happiness
			and prosperity to wife or husband, self and
			children, enmity of relations, gains from gold and precious
			stones, headache, heart disease, nervous breakdown, trouble
			in the anus and much discontent.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Living dependent
			on relations, sycophant acts, acquisition of much wealth.
			loss of few children, gains from lands, contraction of new friendship
			from among the members of the fair sex and liable
			to suffer from venereal complaints.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Perfect
			domestic harmony and happiness, favour from aristocrats,
			progress in education, religious discussions, moral elevation
			and manifestation of a spirit of tolerance and equality.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Misappropriation of private and governmental
			funds and consequent prosecution, wife or husband catching
			consumption and such diseases, death of a few children,
			anxiety about everything, misunderstanding with relations
			and disgrace and disappointments.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Hating all and hated by all, incurring the displeasure of superiors,
			pessimistic about every hope, abject dependency and servile flattery; in the end,
			happiness and prosperity to wife and children.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesKetuPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - Learned discussions, general success, helping
			the suffering, mental depression, promotion, acquisition of
			fertile lands, favour of the superiors and moneyed people,
			moral and religious devotions, vigorous and clear understanding,
			travel on water to distant countries and respect there.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Venus Dasa-->
	<Event>
		<Name>AriesVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus in Aries - Residence in palatial buildings, acquaintance
			with noble personages, wearing good clothes, good
			earnings, spread of fame, much respect, birth of child, happy
			sexual relations and praised by friends and enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>TaurusVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Taurus - A life of great ease and indulgence throughout the period of
			20 years, enjoyment of much happiness, company of beautiful
			girls and joy through association with them, travels on seas to foreign countries
			particularly southern, all ambitions of life fairly realised,
			redemption from debts, symptoms of venereal troubles.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GeminiVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Gemini - Gain of territory, affording
			protection to brothers, sisters, cousins and paternal uncles
			and aunts, gain of vehicles, increase of reputation, children.
			harmony with wife, mental peace and a check over inclination
			to indulge in loose life.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CancerVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Cancer - Paroxysms of grief and terror, destruction of property,
			discontent with relations, increase
			of enemies, loss of wealth, disturbance to good work
			and some mental ease in the end.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LeoVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Leo - Mental disease and
			sorrow, troubles from fires, poisons and hurts, evil women,
			foul language and mental disorder, exile, and aimless wanderings
			in deserts and woods to evade detection by law, dangerous
			sickness to the better half or a child, stigma on self-respect
			due to mean fellows and inclination to conceal true identity.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VirgoVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Virgo - Quarrels with wife or husband and separation from
			him or her, mortgage of all property, trouble in the generative
			organ often leading to surgical operation, symptoms of
			arthritis, troubles relating to nervous breakdown, mental
			unrest, separation from relatives and friends and much grief
			and sorrow.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LibraVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Libra - Great reputation, gain of wealth from
			royal patronage, comforts, good enjoyment of life, luxurious
			invitations and worships of mammon and a period of extreme
			sensuality.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ScorpioVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Scorpio - Hatred for all, many miseries and
			troubles, serious risks, vengeance against relatives, loss of
			wealth and property, mental affliction and imbalance.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SagittariusVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sagittarius - Much fame and name, religious _and philosophical
			studies, recitation of sacred writings, regard for holy people
			and ascetics, success in any undertakings and general prosperity.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>CapricornVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Capricorn - Travels in foreign lands, freedom from
			domestic worries, discussion with learned people, progress
			in general education, acquaintance with low class people,
			development of perverted ideas of social or religious reform
			and success in all endeavors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>AquariusVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Aquarius - Acquisition of
			fresh property, a good library, lands and houses, honours
			and unexpected gains, love for Christian or Islamic literature
			and its studies, stray intercourse with senile women, domestic
			happiness and harmony.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>PiscesVenusPD1</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Pisces - High political power and
			great success, promotion to responsible office, acts of charity
			and generosity, exercise of prudence in official matters and
			perfect happiness in domestic life and smooth-sailing in every
			respect.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD1</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--SUN BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Unpleasantness with relatives and superiors, anxieties,
			headache, pain in the ear, some tendency to urinary or kidney
			troubles, sickness, fear from rulers and enemies, fear of death,
			loss of money, danger to father if the Sun is afflicted, stomachache
			and travels, gains through religious people, mental
			sufferings, a wandering life in a foreign country.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Moon's sub-period-6 months
			Winning favour from superiors, increase in business, fresh
			enterprises, troubles through women, eye troubles, many
			relatives and friends, indulgence in idle pastimes, jaundice
			and kindred ailments, new clothes and ornaments, will be
			happy, healthy, good meals, respect among relatives.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars' sub-period-4 months, 6 days.
			Rheumatic and similar troubles, quarrels, danger of
			enteric fever, dysentery, troubles to relatives, loss of money
			by thefts or wasteful expenses, failures, acquisition of wealth
			in the form of gold and gems, royal favour leading to prosperity,
			contraction and transmission of bilious and other
			diseases, mental worries, danger from fire, ill-health, loss of
			reputation, sorrow.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu's sub-period - 10 months, 24 days.
			Many troubles, changes according to the position of Rahu,
			family disputes, journeys, fear of death, trouble from
			relatives and enemies, loss of peace or mental misery, loss of
			money, sorrows, unsuccessful in all attempts, fear of thieves
			and reptiles, scandals.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter's sub-period-9 months, 18 days.
			Benefits from friends and acquaintances, increase in education,
			employment in high circles, association with people of
			high rank, success through obstacles, birth of a child, wealth
			got through sons (if there is a son), honour to religious people,
			virtuous acts, good traditional observances, good society and
			conversations, reputation, gains and court-honours.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn's sub-period--11 months, 12 days.
			Constant sickness to family members, new enemies, some
			loss of property, bodily ailment, much unhappiness, displacement
			from home accidents, quarrels with relatives, loss
			of money, disease, lacking in energy, ignoble calls, mental
			worries, loans, danger from thieve and rulers.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury's sub-period-IO months, 6 days.
			Gain in money, good reputation, acquisition of new
			clothes and ornaments, new education, trouble through
			relatives, mental distress, depression of spirits, waste of
			money and nervous weakness, no comforts, friends becoming
			enemies, much anxiety and fears, health bad, children ungrateful,
			disputes and trouble from ruler or judge, suffer
			disgrace, many short journeys and wanderings.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu's sub-period - 4 months, 6 days.
			Loss of money, affliction of mind with troubles, fainting
			or nervous exhaustion, mind full of misgivings, a long journey
			to a distant place, change of house due to disputes, troubles
			among relatives and associates, throat disease, mental anguish,
			ophthalmia, serious illness, fear from kings or rulers and
			enemies, diseases, cheated by others.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus sub-period - 1 year.
			Gain of money, respect by rulers and gain of vehicles,
			likelihood of marriage, increase of property, illness, does
			many good works, acquisition of pearls or other precious
			stones, fatigue, addiction to immoral females and profitless
			discussions.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Moon BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun's sub-period - 6 months.
			Feverish complaints, pains in the eyes, success or failure
			according to position of the Sun and the Moon, legal power,
			free from diseases, decadence of enemies, happiness and
			prosperity, jaundice, dropsy, fever, loss of money, travels,
			danger to father and mother, piles, weakness, loss of
			children and friends.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Moon's sub-period- 1O months.
			Devoted attention to learning, love or music, good clothing,
			company of refined society, sound health, good reputation,
			journey to holy places, acquisition of abandoned wealth,
			power, vehicles and lands; marriage, relatives, fortunate
			deeds, inclination to public life, change of residence, birth of
			a child, increase of wealth, prosperity to relatives.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars's sub-period - 7 months.
			Quarrels and litigation among friends and relatives, headlong
			enterprises, danger of disputes between husband and
			wife, between lovers or in regard to marital affairs; disease,
			petulence, loss of money, waste of wealth, trouble from
			brothers and friends, danger from fever and fire, injury from
			instruments or stones, loss of blood and disease to household
			animals.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu's sub-period - 1 year, 6 months.
			Distress of risks from falls and dangerous diseases, waste
			of wealth and loss of relatives and no ease to body, loss of
			money, danger of stirring up enemies, sickness, anxiety, enmity
			of superiors and elders, anxiety and troubles through wife,
			scandals, change of residence, diseases of skin, danger from
			thieves and poison, ill-health to father and mother, suffering
			from hunger.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter's sub-period - 1 year, 4 months.
			Increase of property, plenty of food and comforts, prosperous,
			benefits from superiors such as masters or governors,
			birth. of a child, vehicles, abundance of clothes and ornaments
			and success in undertakings, patronage or rulers, gain or
			property, respect, learned.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn's sub-period - 1 year, 7 months.
			Wife's death or separation, much mental anguish, loss of
			property, loss of friends, ill health, mental trouble due to
			mother, wind and bilious affections, harsh words, and discussion
			with unfriendly people, disease due to indigestion, no peace of mind,
			quarrels with relatives.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury's sub-period - 1 year, 5 months.
			Acquisition of wealth from maternal relatives, new
			clothes and ornaments, settlement of disputes, pleasure
			through children or lover, increase of wealth, accomplishment
			of desires, intellectual achievements, new education, honour
			from rulers, general happiness, enjoyment with females,
			addiction to betting and drinks.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu's sub-period - 7 months.
			Illness to wife, loss of relatives, suffering from stomach
			ache, loss or property, sickness of a feverish nature, danger
			from fire, subject to swellings or eruptions, eye troubles,
			mind filled with cares, public criticism or displeasure, dishonor,
			danger to father, mother and children, scandals
			among equals, eating of prohibited food, bad acts, bad
			company, loss of money and memory.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus's sub-period - 1 year, 8 months.
			Sudden gain from wife, enjoys comforts of agriculture,
			water products and clothing, suffers from diseases inherited
			by mother, sickness, pain, loss of property, enmity, gain of
			houses, good works and good meals, birth of children,
			expenses due to marriage or other auspicious acts.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Mars BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun's sub-period - 4 months, 6 days.
			Gain of money in bad ways, destruction of enemies, good
			reputation, long journey to foreign lands and peace of mind,
			blame, odium of ciders, quarrels with them, sufferings by
			diseases, heartache occasioned by one's own relatives, fever or
			other inflammatory affection, danger of fire, troubles through
			persons in position, many enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Moon's sub-period -7 months.
			Profit, acquisition of wealth, house renovated or some
			improvements effected in it, comforts of wealth, heavy sleep,
			ardent passion, enjoyment by the help or women.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars's sub-period - 4 months, 27 days.
			Great heat, dislike of friends, annoyance from brothers
			and sisters, danger from rulers, failure of all undertakings,
			danger of hurts according to the sign held by Kuja, trouble
			with superiors and some anxiety through strangers, foreigners
			or people abroad and through warlike clan. Danger of open
			violence, quarrel with relations, loss of money, skin disease,
			consumption, loss of blood, fistula, and fissures in anus, loss
			of females and brothers, evil doings and boils.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu's sub-period - 1 year, 18 days.
			Danger from rulers and robbers, loss of wealth, success
			in evil pursuits, suffering from poisonous complaints, loss of
			relatives, danger from skin diseases, change of residence,
			some severe kind of cutaneous disease, journey to a foreign
			country, scandals, loss of cows and buffaloes, illness to wife,
			loss of memory, fear from insects and thieves, falls into well,
			fear from ghosts, affection of gonorrhea, fretting and
			litigation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter's sub-period - 11 months, 6 days.
			Loss of wealth, enemies, end the unfortunate period,
			favour from superiors and persons in position, gain of
			money, birth of children, auspicious celebrations, acquisition
			or wealth through holy people, freedom from illness, public
			reputation, ascendancy and happiness.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn's sub-period - 1 year, 1 month, 9 days.
			Loss of money, diseases, loss of relatives and danger from
			arms or operation, illness leading to misery, evil threatened by
			enemies and robbers, disputes with rulers, loss of wealth,
			quarrel, disputes, litigation, loss of property, cutaneous
			effects. loss of office or position and much anxiety.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury's sub-period- 11 months, 27 days.
			Marriage or inclination to marriage, knowledge and fruits
			of knowledge, wealth, bodily evils disappear, slander, fear of
			insects, poisoned by animals and insects, gain of wealth by
			trade, abundance of houses, trouble from enemies and mental
			worries, service rendered to friends and relatives, new knowledge,
			success in litigation.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu's sub-period - 4 months, 27 days.
			Enmity and quarrels with low people, loss of money due
			to evil works, commission of signs, great sufferings due to
			troubles from relatives and brothers and opposition of bad
			people, family disputes, troubles with one's own kindred
			diseases, poisonous complaints, trouble through women, many
			enemies.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus's sub-period - 1 year, 2 months.
			Acquisition of property, gain of money, domestic happiness,
			successful love affairs, inclination towards religious
			observances and festivities, favourable associations, influenced
			by priests, skin eruptions, boils, pleasure from travelling,
			jewels to wife, clothing, money from relatives and brothers,
			odium.of females and their society, increase of intelligence,
			enjoyment of females and gain of money.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--Rahu BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun's sub-period - 1O months, 24 days.
			Hot fevers, giddiness, fear and enmity of people, quarrels
			in family, benefits from persons in good position, fear and
			suspicion in connection with wife, children and relatives,
			change of position or residence, love of charitable acts,
			contentment, cessation of all violence and outrage of contagious
			diseases, success in examinations, private life happy,
			much reputation and fame, but mental unrest.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Moon - 1 year, 6 months.
			Abundance of enjoyments, good crops, coming in of
			money and communion with kith and kin, loss of relatives,
			loss of money through wife, pains in the limbs, change of
			position or residence, danger of personal hurts, unstability of
			health, sea voyages, gain of lands and money, loss or danger
			to wife and children.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars - 1 year, 18 days.
			Danger from rulers, fires or thieves and by arms, defeat
			in litigation, loss of money due to cousins, difficulties,
			sorrows, danger to the person due to malice of enemies,
			tendency to ease or dissolute habits, disputes and mental
			anxiety, combination of all possible calamities, bewilderment
			in every work and culpable failure of memory.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu - 2 years, 8 months, 12 days.
			Disturbance in mind, anxieties, quarrels among relatives,
			death of partner, master or the head of the family, mental
			anxiety, danger of poisoning, transfer, all sorts of scandals
			and quarrels, fever, bites of insects or wounds by arms, death
			of relatives, going to court as witness, quarrels with parents,
			diseases, illness to wife, failure of intellect, loss of wealth,
			wandering in far-off countries and distress there.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter - 2 years, 4 months, 24 days.
			Total disappearance of enemies and sickness, royal favour,
			acquisition of wealth, birth of children, increase of pleasure,
			gain through nobles or persons in power, benefits and
			comforts from superiors, success in all efforts, marriage in
			the house, increase of enemies, litigations and dips in sacred
			rivers.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn - 2 years, 10 months, 6 days.
			Scandal, danger due to fall of a tree, bad associations,
			divorce of wife or husband, incessant disputes and contests,
			rheumatism, biliousness, etc., throughout: disease due to
			wind and bile, distress of relatives, friends and well-wishers,
			residence in a remote foreign land.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury - 2 years, 6 months, 18 days.
			Many friends and relatives, wife and children, accession
			to wealth or royal favour. In the first 18 months of this
			period very busy, seriously inclined to marry. In the latter
			12 months, enemies increase through his own action, happiness,
			birth of children, acquisition of vehicles, happiness to
			relatives and family, enjoyments with prostitutes, showy,
			gains through trade, fraudulent schemes.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu - 1 year, 18 days.
			Danger, disease in the anus, no good and timely meals,
			epidemic diseases, danger of physical hurts and poison, ill-health
			to children, some swellings in the body, troubles
			through wife, danger from superiors, loss of wealth and
			honour, loss of children, death of cattle and misfortunes of
			all kinds.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus - 3 years.
			Accession to vehicles and things of foreign land, troubles
			from foes, relatives and diseases, acquisition of wealth and
			other advantages, friendly alliances, wife a source of fortune
			and happiness, benefits from superiors or beads above in
			office, liable to deception, false friends, gain in land, birth
			of a child or marriage.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--JUPITER BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun's sub-period - 9 months, 18 days.
			Enemies, victory, ease, great diligence, coming in of
			wealth, royal favour and sound health, gain,good actions or
			fruits of good action, loss of bodily strength.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Tbe Moon's sub-period - 1 year, 4 months.
			Increase of prosperity, gain of fame and fortune, acquisition
			or property, benefits through children, sexual intercourse
			with beautiful women, good meals and clothing, success and
			birth or a female child or marriage to some male member in
			the family, gain of money.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars' sub-period - 11 months, 6 days.
			Disappointments and troubles of various kinds, loss by
			thefts, loss of near and dear relatives, inflammatory disease,
			transfer or leave, failure in hopes and business, wandering,
			high fever, great risks, loss of wealth and depression of mind,
			pilgrimage to temples, acquisition of wealth and fame,
			adventures.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu's sub-period - 2 years, 4 months, 24 days.
			Income through low-caste people, apprehension of diseases,
			possibility of every possible calamity, deprivation of wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter's sub-period - 2 years, 1 month, 18 days.
			Increase of property, domestic happiness, benefit from
			employment or occupation, birth of children, reputation,
			good meals, good deeds, health. royal favour, great diligence,
			success in all attempts, travels, dips in sacred rivers, pilgrimage,
			honour at stake if afflicted.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn's sub-period - 2 years, 6 months, 12 days.
			A feeling of aversion, mental anguish, waste of wealth
			through sons, failure of business, increase of wealth and
			prosperity, pain in the body, rheumatic pains in limbs,
			trouble through wife or partners, failure in profit and credit,
			sorrows, fears, enmity of friends and relatives, adultery,
			unrighteous, a witness in court, quarrels in family, mental
			depression, funeral ceremonies for others,
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury's sub-period - 2 years, 3 months, 6 days.
			Increase of wealth, good and auspicious works in the
			house, communion with relatives, happy, increase of knowledge,
			acquisition of wealth through trade, favour from
			rulers, material comforts, perfect practice of hospitality, gain
			through knowledge in fine arts, birth of a well-favoured child,
			advantages from superiors.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu's sub-period - 11 months, 6 days.
			Pilgrimages to holy shrines, increase of wealth, suffering
			for the sake of several seniors and rulers, death of partner if
			in business, change of residence, separation from relatives
			and friends, may forsake business, poisonous effects, loss of
			wealth, destruction of work, illness, boils.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus's sub-period - 2 years, 8 months.
			Appointment, wealth, reputation, gain of money, savings,
			development of sons and grandsons, jewels, good and
			delicious meals, marital happiness, auspicious works, reunion
			of the family, good success in profession or business, gain of
			land in the month of Taurus or Libra, much enjoyment,
			relatives, friends, peace or mind, acquisition or valuables,
			troubles from females and odium of public.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Saturn BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sun - 11 months, 12 days.
			Loss of wife and children, trouble from rulers or robbers.
			sinking of heart, danger of blood poisoning, haemorrhage of
			the generative system, chronic poisoning, intestinal swellings,
			affliction of the eyes, sickness even to healthy children and
			wife, body full of pain and disorders, danger of death. fear of
			death to father-in-law.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Moon - 1 year, 7 months.
			Increase in cattle, enmity of friends and relatives, cold
			affections, troubles and sickness, family disputes, loss of
			money and property, reduction to great need, mortgage of
			property and its recovery after a lapse of time, death of a
			near relative, sorrow, dislike of relatives, coming in of money,
			windy diseases.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars - 1 year, 1 month, 9 days.
			Some disgrace, serious enmity, strife, much blame,
			wanderings from place to place, unsettled life, many enemies,
			loss of money by fraud or theft, change of residence, serious
			illness, distress to brothers and friends, hot diseases.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu's sub-period - 2 years, 10 months, 6 days.
			Disease in every limb, loss of wealth by rulers, robbers
			and foes, danger of physical hurts, various physical troubles,
			fevers, enemies, increase of troubles.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter - 2 years, 6 months, 12 days.
			Worship of gods and holy people, happiness to family,
			increase in bodily comforts, accomplishment of intentions by
			the help of superiors, increase of family circles, attainment of
			rank.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn's sub-period 3 years, 3 days.
			Brings on diseases, troubles and torments, much mental
			anguish, capacity of kings and free-hooters, loss of wealth,
			fear or poisonous effect to cattle, much sufferings to family,
			fever, wind or phlegm, bodily ailments and colic, body
			languishes, loss of money and children, serious enmities,
			dispute and troubles from relatives, blood and bilious complaints,
			quarrels in family, loss of money, mental derangement.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury's sub-period - 2 years, 8 months, 9 days.
			Charitable works, gain of wealth, birth of children,
			increase of knowledge in some branch, prosperity to children,
			success to relatives, general prosperity, favours and approbation
			from superiors, increase of happiness, wealth and fame,
			benefits occurring from acts of piety and customary religious
			observances, agriculture and commerce.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu's sub-period - 1 year, I month, 9 days.
			Rheumatism or sickness, danger of poison, danger from
			sons, loss of money, contentions and quarrels with vile and
			wicked people, dread of evil dreams, quarrels in family.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus - 3 years, 2 months.
			Auspicious, general happiness, attentions and favours
			from others, gifts, profits in business, increase of family
			members, victory over enemies, success in life, goodwill of
			relatives, accession to wife's property and wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Mercury BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sun - 1O months, 6 days.
			Pains in bead and stomach, enmity of people, loss of
			respect, danger of fire, anxieties, sickness to wire, troubles
			from enemies, many obstacles, troubles through superiors,
			acquisition of wealth.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Moon - 1 year, 5 months.
			Loss of health, some swellings or hurts in the limbs,
			quarrels and troubles through women, many difficulties, gain
			of money through ladies and agriculture and trade, success,
			happiness, diseases, ill-will of enemies, miscarriage of every
			concern, risk from quadrupeds.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars sub-period - 11 months, 27 days.
			Disappearance of all dangers diseases or enemies, fame
			derived from acts of charity and beneficence, royal favour,
			danger from jaundice or bilious fever, affections of the blood,
			neuralgic pains and headaches, troubles through neighbors,
			sickness, wounds or hurts, quarrels, addiction to drinks,
			betting and prostitutes, boils and hurts of arms, travels in
			forests and villages, sorrows, royal disfavour, imprisonment.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu - 2 years, 6 months, 18 days.
			Intercourse with servants and prostitutes, skin diseases,
			sufferings from hot diseases, bad company and dirty meals.
			change or present position, fear and danger through foreigners,
			disputes concerning property, failure in litigation, evil dreams.
			headaches, sickness and loss of appetite. wealth from friends
			and relatives, happiness, new earnings.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter - 2 years, 3 months 6 days.
			Hatred of friends, relatives and elders, wealth, liable to
			diseases, acquisition of land and wealth, gain by trade, reputation,
			good happiness, good credit, benefits from superiors,
			birth of a child or marriage.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn - 2 years, 8 months, 9 days.
			Bad luck. stranger to success and happiness, severe reversal,
			enmity, pain in the part governed by Saturn, downfall or disgrace
			to relatives, mind full of evil forebodings and distress.
			rear from diseases, loans, loss of children, destruction of
			family, scandals, troubles from foreigners, earnings through
			evil ways, acts of charity and beneficence, acquisition of
			wealth, material comforts through petty chiefs, failure in
			agricultural operations.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury's sub-period - 2 years, 4 months, 27
			Acquisition of beautiful house and apparel, money through
			relatives, success in every undertaking, the birth of a brother
			or sister, increase in family, gain in business, good mind
			charitable acts, learning of mathematics and arts.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu - 11 months, 27 days.
			Sorrow, disease, loss of work and Dharma, bilious sickness,
			aimless wandering, loss of property, misfortune to
			relatives, troubles through doctors, mental anxiety, trouble
			from relatives, mental agony, loss of comfort, dread of enemy,
			failure in business.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus - 2 years, 10 months.
			Observance of duty, conformable to religion and morality,
			acquisition of wealth, clothes and jewels, birth or good
			children, happiness in married state, relatives prosper, trade
			increases, knowledge gained, return from a long journey, if
			not married, betrothal in this period, health, ornaments,
			vehicles, house, money gained.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Ketu BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun's sub-period - 4 months, 6 days.
			Disappointment, physical pain, exile in foreign country,
			peril and obstruction in every business, increase of knowledge,
			sickness in family, long journey and return, anxiety about
			wife's health.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Moon's sub-period-7 months.
			Disputes about fair sex, trouble through children,
			gains and financial success, diseases of biliousness and cold,
			loss of relatives and money, destruction of wealth and
			distress of mind.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars' sub-period - 4 months, 27 days.
			Odium of sons, wife and younger brothers, loss of relatives,
			trouble from diseases, foes and bad rulers, path of
			progress obstructed, fear and anxiety, disputes and contests
			of different kinds, enemies arise, danger of disputes and
			destruction through females, sufferings from fever, fear of
			robbers, death, imprisonment, urinary diseases,
			loss and difficulties
			and surgical operations.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu - 1 year, 18 days.
			Loss of lands, imprisonment, quarrel with friends, danger
			of blood poisoning, danger of ruin, loss of property, fame
			and honour, rear of kings and robbers, sorrow, ruin of all
			business, adultery with mean women.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter - 11 months, 6 days.
			Exemption from ailments, acquisition of lands and birth
			of children, profitable transactions, association with people of
			good position, danger of poison, wife an object of pleasure,
			if unmarried marriage takes place.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn - 1 year, 1 month, 9 days.
			Loss of wife, danger from enemies, imprisonment, loss of
			wealth, indigestion, property in danger or ruin, heavy loss in
			different ways, change of residence, some cutaneous diseases.
			anxiety owing to sickness of partner misgivings in the heart,
			mental anguish, difference of opinion with relations, exile in
			foreign countries.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury - 11 months 27 days.
			Society of relatives, friends and the like, material gains
			from knowledge, danger from relatives, anxiety on account of
			children, failure in plans, deception, jealousy, falsehood, and
			knowledge.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu's sub-period - 4 months, 27 days.
			Fear of death of wife or children, loss of wealth and
			happiness, mental troubles, separation from relatives, subject
			to some estrangement, restraint or detention, danger of
			poison.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus - 1 year, 2 months.
			Wealth and happiness, birth of a child, efforts crowned
			with success, in the end sickness, wife ill, illness to children,
			quarrels, loss of relatives and friends, fever and dysentery.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Venus BHUKTI-->
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSunPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Sun - 1 year.
			Anxious about everything, prosperity collapses, troubles
			with wife, children, land, family, disputes and quarrels,
			diseases affecting head, belly and eyes, damage in respect of
			agriculture.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMoonPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Moon - 1 year, 8 months.
			Gains of females, education, knowledge, money, children
			and vehicles, worship of God, accomplishments of desires,
			troubles through wife, domestic happiness afterwards, pain
			and disease due to inflammation of nervous tissue and from
			lust and other passions of human nature.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMarsPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mars - 1 year, 2 months.
			Flow of bile, disease of the eyes, great exertion, much
			income, acquisition or wealth, marriage, acquisition of lands,
			venereal diseases, danger from arms, exile in foreign places,
			atheistic tendencies, increase of property through the influence
			of females, negligence of duty, bent on pleasure and passion,
			temporary affection of eyes.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusRahuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Rahu - 3 years.
			Meditation, seclusion, quarrels among relatives and his
			people, entire change of surroundings, schemes of deception.
			miserliness, acquisition of lost property, dislike of relatives.
			evil from friends and injury by fire.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusJupiterPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Jupiter - 2 years, 8 months.
			Means of livelihood settled, gains from profession, benefits
			through superiors or employers or persons ruled by Jupiter
			fame, anxiety, quarrels with saints and religious men, gain of
			knowledge, end of dependence, worship of certain inferior
			natural forces, happiness and health, marriages, sexual intercourse,
			increase of family reputation and good deeds, wealth.
			ultimate happiness, wife and children suffer in the end.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSaturnPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturn - 3 years, 2 months
			Sexual intercourse with females advanced in age, accession
			to lands and wealth, disappearance of enemies, affection of
			excretory system, piles, etc., rheumatic pains in legs and
			bands, danger to eye sight, distaste for food, loss of appetite,
			physical condition poor, loss of money, wanderings, servitude,
			bolting and gambling, addiction to liquor, bad company, etc.,
			ill-health, loss of memory, impotence.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMercuryPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Mercury - 2 years, 10 months.
			Association with prostitutes, enjoyments, knowledge,
			mathematical learning, success in litigations, inclination to
			learn music, piles and other hot ailments, pleasure through
			wife and children, increase of wealth, gain of knowledge in
			aru and sciences, wealth, royal favour, prosperity on a large
			scale and sound health.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusKetuPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Ketu - 1 year, 2 months.
			Discordance, death of relatives, injury inflicted by enemies,
			misgivings in heart, deprivation of wealth, troubles through
			wife, danger from quadrupeds, illness to partner or a member
			of the family, accidental blood poisoning, delirious fits, weakness
			in body and mind, gradual loss of wealth, loss of
			relatives, bad company, abode in seclusion, manifold sorrows,
			but happiness in the end.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusVenusPD2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Venus - 3 years, 4 months.
			Success, good servants and good many pleasures, money
			plentiful. disappearance of enemies, attainment of fame and
			birth of children.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD2</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Nature & description filled in by calculator-->

	<!--SUN PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSunPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MOON PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMoonPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MARS PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMarsPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--RAHU PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusRahuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--JUPITER PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusJupiterPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--SATURN PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSaturnPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MERCURY PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMercuryPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--KETU PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusKetuPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--VENUS PD3 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusVenusPD3</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD3</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Nature & description filled in by calculator-->

	<!--SUN PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSunPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MOON PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMoonPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MARS PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMarsPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--RAHU PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusRahuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--JUPITER PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusJupiterPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--SATURN PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSaturnPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MERCURY PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMercuryPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--KETU PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusKetuPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--VENUS PD4 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusVenusPD4</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD4</Tag>
	</Event>



	<!--Nature & description filled in by calculator-->

	<!--SUN PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSunPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MOON PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMoonPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MARS PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMarsPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--RAHU PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusRahuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--JUPITER PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusJupiterPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--SATURN PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSaturnPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MERCURY PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMercuryPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--KETU PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusKetuPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--VENUS PD5 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusVenusPD5</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD5</Tag>
	</Event>



	<!--Nature & description filled in by calculator-->

	<!--SUN PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSunPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MOON PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMoonPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MARS PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMarsPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--RAHU PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusRahuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--JUPITER PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusJupiterPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--SATURN PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSaturnPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MERCURY PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMercuryPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--KETU PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusKetuPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--VENUS PD6 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusVenusPD6</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD6</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Nature & description filled in by calculator-->

	<!--SUN PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSunPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MOON PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMoonPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MARS PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMarsPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--RAHU PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusRahuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--JUPITER PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusJupiterPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--SATURN PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSaturnPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MERCURY PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMercuryPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--KETU PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusKetuPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--VENUS PD7 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusVenusPD7</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD7</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--Nature & description filled in by calculator-->

	<!--SUN PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSunPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MOON PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMoonPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MARS PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMarsPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--RAHU PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusRahuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--JUPITER PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusJupiterPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--SATURN PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercurySaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusSaturnPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--MERCURY PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusMercuryPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--KETU PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusKetuPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>

	<!--VENUS PD8 -->
	<Event>
		<Name>SunVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MoonVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MarsVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>RahuVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>JupiterVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SaturnVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>MercuryVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>KetuVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>VenusVenusPD8</Name>
		<Nature/>
		<Description/>
		<Tag>Dasa,PD8</Tag>
	</Event>




	<!--Dasa Special Rules-->
	<Event>
		<Name>Lord6And8Dasa</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Dasa period of the lords of the 6th and the 8th
			produce harmful results unless they acquire beneficence
			otherwise.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Lord5And9Dasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The periods of lords of the 5th and the 9th are said
			to be good, so much so that the periods of planets, which are
			joined or otherwise related with them, are also supposed to
			give rise to good.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Lord5And9DasaBhukti</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The sub-period of the lord of the 5th in the major
			period of the lord of the 9th or vice versa is supposed to
			produce good effects.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BhuktiDasaLordInBadHouses</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Unfavourable results will be realised when the sub-lord
			and the major lord are situated in the 6th and the 8th or
			the 12th and the 2nd from each other respectively.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Lord2Dasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Lord of the 2nd in his Dasa gives wealth
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Lord3Dasa</Name>
		<Nature>Neutral</Nature>
		<Description>
			Lord of the 3rd during his Dasa gives new friends,
			help to brothers, leadership, and physical pain (if afflicted).
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>LagnaLordDasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			When Lagna (Ascendant) is powerful, during the Dasa
			of lord of Lagna, favourable results can be expected to occur
			- such as rise in profession, good health and general prosperity.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Saturn4thDasa</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Dasa period of Saturn, if it happens to be the 4th
			Dasa, will be unfavourable.
			If Saturn is strong and favorably disposed,
			the evil effects get considerably modified.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>Jupiter6thDasa</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Dasa period of Jupiter will be unfavourable if it
			happens to be the 6th Dasa.
			If Saturn is strong and favorably disposed,
			the evil effects get considerably modified.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>

	<Event>
		<Name>ElevatedSunDasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			If the Sun is elevated, he displays wisdom, gets
			money, attains fame and happiness
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunWithLord9Or10Dasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun in good position, in own house or joined with lord of 9 or
			10 - happiness, gains, riches, honours
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunWithLord5Dasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun with lord of 5 - birth of children.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunWithLord2Dasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun when related to lord of 2 - becomes rich, earns money, secures
			property, gains, favours from influential persons.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>SunBadPositionDasa</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Sun when debilitated or occupies the 6th or the
			8th house or in cojunction with evil planets contracts evil diseases, loss of wealth, suffers from reverses
			in employment, penalty and becomes ill.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>ExaltedSunDasa</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Dasa of the Sun in deep exaltation : Sudden
			gains in cattle and wealth, much travelling in eastern
			countries, residence in foreign countries, quarrels
			among friends and relations, pleasure trios and picnic
			parties and lovely women.
		</Description>
		<Tag>DasaSpecialRules</Tag>
	</Event>


	<!--HOUSE BUILDING-->

	<Event>
		<Name>BadLunarMonthForBuilding</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			No house-building should be commenced in the lunar months of
			Jyeshta, Ashadha, Bhadrapada, Aswayuja, Margasira, Pushya and
			Phalguna as they connote respectively death, destruction, disease,
			quarrels and misunderstandings, loss of wealth, incendiarism and
			physical danger
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodSunSignForBuilding</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			For building work,
			the Sun should occupy fixed signs or
			at least movable signs.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadSunSignForBuilding</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			No building work should be undertaken when
			the Sun is in common signs.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodLunarDayForBuilding</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for building:
			- All odd tithis (lunar days) except the 9th are good.
			- Of the even tithis the 2nd, 6th and 10th are auspicious.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodWeekDayForBuilding</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Good for building:
			Monday, Wednesday, Thursday and  Friday are the best.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadLunarPhaseForBuilding</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Moon is waning.
			Even Monday should be rejected when the Moon is waning.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadWeekDayForBuilding</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Saturday should be rejected as it connots frequent thefts. Sunday
			should also be avoided unless the day is otherwise very auspicious.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>BadWeekDayForRepairs</Name>
		<Nature>Bad</Nature>
		<Description>
			Do not commence repairs on Tuesdays.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodYogaForRepairs</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			Friday at a moment when Lagna is Taurus or Libra and Monday when Cancer is
			rising are very suitable for beginning repairs
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>
	<Event>
		<Name>GoodYogaForRepairs2</Name>
		<Nature>Good</Nature>
		<Description>
			The Lagna must be occupied by a benefic and the Moon should be in an aquatic sign.
		</Description>
		<Tag>Building</Tag>
	</Event>

</Root>